{"id":51,"text":"Chelsea have triggered the release clause in the contract of Leeds United midfielder Tyler Adams, sources have confirmed to 90min. The Whites were relegated from the Premier League last season, activating a  £20m clause that allows Adams to leave Elland Road if a bidding club is prepared to pay in full. 90min revealed on Monday that Chelsea had contacted the representatives of Adams over a move to west London, and personal terms are now being discussed with the 24-year-old United States international. The Blues have also informed Leeds of their intention to pay Adams' release clause in full, and he is expected to undergo a medical within the next 24 hours. Adams is seen as a shrewd signing by those in charge at Stamford Bridge, who are working to provide manager Mauricio Pochettino with the midfield reinforcements he has publicly requested this summer. feed Chelsea are working on a number of midfield signings and recently launched a bid to rival Liverpool for Southampton midfielder Romeo Lavia, who has been on the Blues' radar for over 12 months now. After Liverpool saw a  £46m bid rejected for Lavia, Chelsea put forward an offer of  £48m, though that remains short of Southampton's  £50m asking price. Chelsea are also continuing to work on an agreement for Brighton midfielder Moises Caicedo, whose  £100m asking price has so far proven problematic. Liverpool have also made late contact with Brighton over potentially rivalling Chelsea's latest offer, which sat at  £80m, but have not progressed talks to the point of making a formal offer.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[61,73,"ORG"],[85,96,"PER"],[124,129,"ORG"],[131,141,"ORG"],[166,180,"ORG"],[208,212,"MON"],[232,237,"PER"],[247,258,"ORG"],[305,310,"ORG"],[335,342,"ORG"],[380,385,"PER"],[401,412,"LOC"],[478,491,"ORG"],[507,516,"ORG"],[536,541,"ORG"],[568,573,"PER"],[665,670,"PER"],[721,736,"ORG"],[773,792,"PER"],[870,877,"ORG"],[960,969,"ORG"],[974,985,"ORG"],[997,1008,"PER"],[1026,1035,"ORG"],[1073,1082,"ORG"],[1090,1094,"MON"],[1112,1117,"PER"],[1119,1126,"ORG"],[1152,1156,"MON"],[1187,1200,"ORG"],[1202,1206,"MON"],[1221,1228,"ORG"],[1277,1285,"ORG"],[1297,1311,"PER"],[1320,1325,"MON"],[1370,1379,"ORG"],[1413,1421,"ORG"],[1449,1458,"ORG"],[1487,1491,"MON"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":52,"text":"Barcelona vice-president Rafa Yuste has confirmed that Ousmane Dembele is on the verge of completing a move to Paris Saint-Germain. The France international was not expected to leave or push for a move away from Catalonia this summer, but PSG triggered his    50m ( £43m) release clause shortly before it expired in July and proceeded to discuss personal terms. During these negotiations, Dembele was called out in public by Barcelona head coach Xavi and club captain Sergi Roberto, who expressed their shock at the sudden move. 90min reported on August 3 that PSG had hoped to wrap up a deal before the end of last week, but a deal has dragged on and reports from the Spanish press suggested talks had stalled. feed But after Dembele was omitted from Barca's squad to take on Tottenham Hotspur in the annual Joan Gamper Trophy on Tuesday night, vice-president Yuste insisted that the transfer will go ahead and confirmation of an agreement is close. \"We're on the verge of resolving Dembele deal with Paris Saint-Germain as all parties want to seal it as soon as possible,\" Yuste said. \"Dembele is not with us tonight as we hope to settle the matter soon. We are on it.\" With money raised from the sales of Dembele and midfielder Franck Kessie, 90min understands that Barcelona will make a fresh move to sign Joao Cancelo, while they remain interested in his Manchester City teammate Bernardo Silva.","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[25,35,"PER"],[55,70,"PER"],[111,130,"ORG"],[136,142,"ORG"],[212,221,"LOC"],[239,242,"ORG"],[260,263,"MON"],[266,270,"MON"],[316,320,"DAT"],[389,396,"PER"],[425,434,"ORG"],[446,450,"PER"],[468,481,"PER"],[529,534,"ORG"],[547,555,"DAT"],[561,564,"ORG"],[727,734,"PER"],[752,759,"ORG"],[777,794,"ORG"],[809,827,"ORG"],[861,866,"PER"],[984,991,"PER"],[1002,1021,"ORG"],[1075,1080,"PER"],[1088,1095,"PER"],[1208,1215,"PER"],[1231,1244,"PER"],[1246,1251,"ORG"],[1269,1278,"ORG"],[1310,1322,"PER"],[1360,1375,"ORG"],[1385,1399,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":53,"text":"Manchester United goalkeeper Matej Kovar is on the verge of a permanent transfer away from the club as he undergoes a medical with Bayer Leverkusen, sources have confirmed to 90min. Now 23, Kovar has been with United since the age of 17. He joined from home-town club Solvacko in 2018 and has been loaned out to Swindon Town, Burton Albion and Sparta Prague during that time. It was his loan at Sparta last season that brought Kovar to wider attention. It was his very first year as a top flight starter and he helped the club win the Czech First League and return to the Champions League qualifying rounds. 90min reported in May that Kovar   s form on loan had caught the eye of his parent club. There were glowing reviews coming back from Prague and he was included in the thought process regarding the goalkeeping position long before Andre Onana was eventually signed. At a time when David de Gea was widely expected to sign a new contract at Old Trafford, United staff considered the possibility that Kovar could emerge as the Spaniard   s chief back-up and limit the need to spend big on a new goalkeeper. feed However, De Gea   s contract offer was later withdrawn and revised, ultimately leading to him leaving the club as a free agent. It accelerated the need for a readymade number one and so the club spent handsomely to sign Onana from Inter, reuniting the Cameroonian with Erik ten Hag. Kovar was briefly involved in United   s pre-season programme, playing 135 minutes of the opening two summer friendlies against Leeds and Lyon. But his immediate future now lies elsewhere. 90min understands that a  £7.8m (   9m) transfer fee has been agreed with Bayer Leverkusen and that a medical to complete the transfer is already being undertaken. Ties with Kovar have not been fully cut though, as United have retained a buy-back clause that could see him return to Manchester. Leverkusen finished sixth in the Bundesliga last season following a remarkable turnaround once Xabi Alonso was appointed head coach, having been flirting with relegation initially. It means that Kovar could have the chance to play Europa League football in 2023\/24. He will compete with veteran Finland international and current Leverkusen captain Lukas Hradecky.","label":[[0,17,"ORG"],[29,40,"PER"],[131,147,"ORG"],[175,180,"ORG"],[190,195,"PER"],[210,216,"ORG"],[263,276,"ORG"],[280,284,"DAT"],[312,324,"ORG"],[326,339,"ORG"],[344,358,"ORG"],[395,401,"ORG"],[427,432,"PER"],[535,553,"ORG"],[572,588,"ORG"],[608,613,"ORG"],[626,629,"DAT"],[635,640,"PER"],[741,747,"LOC"],[838,849,"PER"],[888,900,"PER"],[947,959,"LOC"],[961,967,"ORG"],[1006,1011,"PER"],[1126,1132,"PER"],[1337,1342,"PER"],[1348,1353,"ORG"],[1386,1398,"PER"],[1400,1405,"PER"],[1430,1436,"ORG"],[1528,1533,"ORG"],[1538,1542,"ORG"],[1589,1594,"ORG"],[1615,1620,"MON"],[1625,1627,"MON"],[1663,1679,"ORG"],[1763,1768,"PER"],[1804,1810,"PER"],[1872,1883,"LOC"],[1884,1894,"ORG"],[1917,1927,"ORG"],[1979,1990,"PER"],[2079,2084,"PER"],[2115,2128,"ORG"],[2141,2148,"DAT"],[2179,2186,"LOC"],[2213,2223,"ORG"],[2232,2246,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":54,"text":"Jurgen Klopp has admitted Liverpool did not expect to have the money to pursue Moises Caicedo when they pulled out of the race to sign Jude Bellingham earlier this summer. Bellingham was Liverpool's top target heading into the summer transfer window but, when the true cost of the deal was set, the Reds ultimately pulled out and Bellingham ended up joining Real Madrid for an initial  £88.5m. Since then, however, Liverpool agreed to the surprise sales of both Jordan Henderson and Fabinho, who moved to Saudi Arabia, and Klopp admitted that unplanned income played a part in the  £111m move for Caicedo. \"I can confirm that the deal with the club is agreed,\" Klopp told a press conference when asked about the Caicedo bid. \"What did change? We are a club, we have not endless resources, we didn't expect a couple of things happening in the summer - Hendo, Fab, stuff like this. We didn't think about this before the summer to be honest, and when it happened, we gave it a go. Obviously the club was really stretched, to be honest.\" feed Klopp went on to insist he knew nothing else about Liverpool's move for Caicedo, stressing he had \"no idea\" whether the Ecuador international was due for a medical on Friday. The pursuit of Caicedo came after Liverpool had a third bid rejected for Southampton midfielder Romeo Lavia. Chelsea went on to offer  £48m for the Belgian shortly before the Reds took control of the Caicedo race. Asked whether signing Caicedo would end Liverpool's pursuit of Lavia, Klopp urged fans to wait and see how things play out. \"Let's talk about that if it happens,\" he said. \"It's nothing I can really say, that's the truth. Let's do it step by step, let's see what happens in the next hours or days and then go from there.\"","label":[[0,12,"PER"],[26,35,"ORG"],[79,93,"PER"],[135,150,"PER"],[172,182,"PER"],[187,198,"ORG"],[295,303,"ORG"],[330,340,"PER"],[358,369,"ORG"],[386,392,"MON"],[415,424,"ORG"],[462,478,"PER"],[483,490,"PER"],[505,517,"LOC"],[523,528,"PER"],[582,587,"MON"],[597,604,"PER"],[661,666,"PER"],[712,719,"PER"],[851,856,"PER"],[858,861,"PER"],[1039,1044,"PER"],[1090,1101,"ORG"],[1111,1118,"PER"],[1159,1166,"ORG"],[1229,1236,"PER"],[1248,1257,"ORG"],[1287,1298,"ORG"],[1310,1321,"PER"],[1323,1330,"ORG"],[1349,1353,"MON"],[1385,1393,"ORG"],[1414,1421,"PER"],[1450,1457,"PER"],[1468,1479,"ORG"],[1491,1496,"PER"],[1498,1503,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":55,"text":"Chelsea have confirmed that winger Angelo Gabriel has joined French outfit Strasbourg on loan for the 2023\/24 season. The 18-year-old signed from Santos in his native Brazil back in July for a fee believed to be in the region of  £13m. Gabriel featured three times during Chelsea's five-match tour of the United States in pre-season but has now completed a move to Ligue 1. Strasbourg, who are managed by Patrick Vieira, were recently acquired by Chelsea's BlueCo ownership group, with other young summer signings expected to be sent on loan to the Stade de la Meinau before the end of the transfer window. feed 90min understands that Chelsea are working on a deal to sign Gabriel's former Santos teammate, Deivid Washington, and it is possible they reunite at Strasbourg. Chelsea confirmed an extended rejigging of squad numbers prior to confirmation of Gabriel's loan, with the winger not handed one ahead of the new season and suggesting a move away was close to being finalised. The Blues also revealed that they will be without Christopher Nkunku for the first few months of the season after he sustained knee ligament damage.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[35,49,"PER"],[75,85,"ORG"],[102,109,"DAT"],[146,152,"ORG"],[167,173,"LOC"],[182,186,"DAT"],[230,234,"MON"],[236,243,"PER"],[272,281,"ORG"],[301,318,"LOC"],[365,372,"ORG"],[374,384,"ORG"],[405,419,"PER"],[447,456,"ORG"],[545,567,"ORG"],[612,617,"ORG"],[635,642,"ORG"],[673,682,"PER"],[690,696,"ORG"],[707,724,"PER"],[761,771,"ORG"],[773,780,"ORG"],[855,864,"PER"],[983,992,"ORG"],[1033,1051,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":56,"text":"Manchester United manager Erik ten Hag has insisted the club were 'professional' and followed 'careful processes' in their transfer recruitment this summer. The Red Devils recently completed the signing of Atalanta's Rasmus Hojlund for a fee that could reach  £72m. He is expected to become their starting striker once he returns to full fitness following a back injury, United have had a long-standing interest in Harry Kane, but they did not make any advances to Tottenham Hotspur this summer, and the 30-year-old is now set to join Bayern Munich after the two clubs agreed on an  £86.4m fee. Ahead of Monday's Premier League opener at home to Wolves, Ten Hag was asked about Kane's move to the Bundesliga and Man Utd's own interest - with the Dutchman admitting his exit is a blow to England's top flight. \"I don't think that I have to go into that discussion or give an opinion about that,\" Ten Hag said. \"We are professional, the processes we do are really careful. \"We consider a lot of things but finally we make decisions, we don't take decisions overnight, there is a strategy in every decision behind and we are happy with the squad we have behind us now. feed \"We have chosen a striker and we are really happy with our choice. He [Kane] is a great striker, clear. A goal-maker and apart from that he has all the conditions and abilities that you want to see in a striker. \"It's a miss for the Premier League, absolutely.\" United ironically travel to Tottenham next Saturday for their second Premier League fixture of the season, and could instead up against a forward line led by Son Heung-min and Richarlison, who spent most of last season on the bench despite costing the north Londoners  £60m when joining from Everton. Hojlund won't be available for the Red Devils, as he nurses his back injury, and that could put the onus on Marcus Rashford to again score the goals for Ten Hag's side. The 25-year-old scored a career-best 30 in all competitions last season to earn a new five-year contract and status as the highest-paid player at the club.","label":[[0,17,"ORG"],[26,38,"PER"],[157,171,"ORG"],[206,216,"ORG"],[217,231,"PER"],[260,264,"MON"],[371,377,"ORG"],[415,425,"PER"],[465,482,"ORG"],[535,548,"ORG"],[583,589,"MON"],[613,627,"ORG"],[646,652,"ORG"],[654,661,"PER"],[678,684,"PER"],[693,707,"ORG"],[712,721,"ORG"],[787,796,"LOC"],[895,902,"PER"],[1242,1246,"PER"],[1400,1418,"ORG"],[1433,1439,"ORG"],[1461,1470,"ORG"],[1502,1516,"ORG"],[1591,1604,"PER"],[1609,1620,"PER"],[1702,1706,"MON"],[1725,1732,"ORG"],[1734,1741,"PER"],[1765,1779,"ORG"],[1842,1857,"PER"],[1887,1896,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":57,"text":"Liverpool captain Virgil van Dijk has admitted that he understands why fans have \"doubts\" over the club's transfer business this summer.  The Reds made two early splashes in the transfer market this summer by signing Alexis Mac Allister and Dominik Szoboszlai for a combined  £95m, which could grow to  £115m with the former's add-ons. Liverpool have largely struggled to get any other deals over the line however, seeing three bids rejected by Southampton for Romeo Lavia and interest in defensive options such as Jurrien Timber fizzle out - with the defender instead joining Arsenal.  Coupled with that, the Reds have also let a huge number of first-team players leave the club, particularly in midfielder as captain Jordan Henderson and vice-captain Fabinho both joined Saudi Pro League teams, and the likes of James Milner, Naby Keita and Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain all left as free agents. Long-serving forward Roberto Firmino has also moved on. feed All of this has ultimately led to Liverpool fans being rather unimpressed with the club's transfer business and new club captain Van Dijk admitted that he understands their concerns. \"I can definitely understand it in some ways but I'm not a very negative person,\" he said. \"Obviously, when a lot of players are leaving, when your captain and vice-captain is leaving, and at the moment, there are only two incomings. And the way we have been playing, in possession really good but defensively when you concede goals it's not as good, I can understand some people having doubts. \"Let's see if more players are coming in and then we have to be ready again for a long season. It will be very tough if we look at the teams around us, but we want to be up there again, we want to be challenging again.  \"We have to be confident, we should be confident, and we should still be learning each and every day. There have been characters leaving, players who have played a big part in the success, but others have to step up. That's a nice challenge in my opinion. We should be excited.\" The Reds kick-off their 2023\/24 Premier League campaign on Sunday against Chelsea at Stamford Bridge. ","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[18,33,"PER"],[138,146,"ORG"],[217,236,"PER"],[241,259,"PER"],[276,280,"MON"],[303,308,"MON"],[336,345,"ORG"],[445,456,"ORG"],[461,472,"PER"],[515,529,"PER"],[577,584,"ORG"],[606,614,"ORG"],[719,735,"PER"],[753,760,"PER"],[773,789,"ORG"],[814,826,"PER"],[828,838,"PER"],[843,866,"PER"],[913,928,"PER"],[987,996,"ORG"],[1082,1090,"PER"],[2030,2038,"ORG"],[2054,2061,"DAT"],[2062,2076,"ORG"],[2104,2111,"ORG"],[2115,2130,"LOC"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":58,"text":"Nice manager Francesco Farioli has confessed Manchester United's interest in centre-back Jean-Clair Todibo could leave them powerless to keep the Frenchman. United are on the cusp of selling Harry Maguire to West Ham United for  £30m and have identified former Barcelona defender Todibo as a potential replacement for the Englishman. One of the top performers in Ligue 1 last season, Todibo is rated incredibly highly by everyone at Nice, including new manager Farioli, but while the boss wants to keep Todibo, he admitted he could not guarantee no business would be done. \"I also have two vice-captains Khephren Thuram and Jean-Clair Todibo who are among the best players in the team,\" Farioli told the media. \"We would like both players to stay until the end of the season, but you cannot escape the reality of the transfer window. We'll see what happens. As long as they're here, I'm enjoying having them.\" feed He continued: \"Of course we would like Todibo to stay, but it can be complicated. We have to wait to see who will want to buy him and if everyone finds an agreement there.  \"He is a leader, a very strong player mentally, he has improved a lot and he is ready to reach the very top level.\" United have drawn up a sizeable list of potential replacements for Maguire. Alongside Todibo, there is also interest in Torino's Perr Schuurs and Everton's Jarrad Branthwaite, while Bayer Leverkusen's Edmond Tapsoba is seen as an expensive alternative. The Red Devils have also been offered the chance to sign versatile Bayern Munich defender Benjamin Pavard, who is in the final year of his contract and is expected to be available for a fee similar to the  £30m United are in line to receive for Maguire.","label":[[0,4,"ORG"],[13,30,"PER"],[45,64,"ORG"],[89,106,"PER"],[157,163,"ORG"],[191,204,"PER"],[208,223,"ORG"],[229,233,"MON"],[261,270,"ORG"],[280,286,"PER"],[363,370,"ORG"],[384,390,"PER"],[433,437,"ORG"],[461,468,"PER"],[503,509,"PER"],[604,619,"PER"],[624,641,"PER"],[687,694,"PER"],[954,960,"PER"],[1204,1210,"ORG"],[1271,1278,"PER"],[1290,1296,"PER"],[1324,1332,"ORG"],[1333,1345,"PER"],[1350,1359,"ORG"],[1360,1378,"PER"],[1386,1404,"ORG"],[1405,1419,"PER"],[1457,1471,"ORG"],[1524,1537,"ORG"],[1547,1562,"PER"],[1663,1667,"MON"],[1668,1674,"ORG"],[1702,1709,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":59,"text":"Athletico Paranaense CEO Alexandre Mattos has insisted that Vitor Roque will not join Barcelona until January 2024.  Barcelona confirmed the  £34m (   40m) signing of Roque in July, with the agreement seeing the teenage striker remain with his current employers until the end of the calendar year before making the move to Spain in January 2024. Rumours have began to swirl in recent weeks that Barca could try to bring the move forward due to the sale of Ousmane Dembele to Paris Saint-Germain, with manager Xavi now potentially needing more reinforcements after the Frenchman's surprise departure. However, Mattos has now shut down the speculation, insisting Roque will not leave the club until 2024. feed \"There's no chance for Vitor Roque to leave and join Barcelona in August,\" he told Fabrizio Romano. \"He will leave in January, that was the pact with Barca and it will be respected.  \"We need him for the final 20 games and to qualify for the 2024 Copa Libertadores.\"  In a recent interview, Roque's agent discussed how his client is already preparing for his move to the Catalan club. \"Vitor is very calm, he will not have any anxiety. He is already doing Catalan classes, he wants to arrive speaking Catalan and Spanish. Everything will work out,\" agent Andre Cury said. \"When his signing was closed he was elated, but he is already focused on Athletico Paranaense. He will know how to wait for the right moment to become the main man at Barca and make history.\"","label":[[0,20,"ORG"],[25,41,"PER"],[60,71,"PER"],[86,95,"ORG"],[102,114,"DAT"],[117,126,"PER"],[142,146,"MON"],[151,154,"MON"],[167,172,"PER"],[176,180,"DAT"],[323,328,"LOC"],[332,344,"DAT"],[395,400,"ORG"],[456,471,"PER"],[475,494,"ORG"],[509,513,"PER"],[609,615,"PER"],[661,666,"PER"],[697,701,"DAT"],[731,742,"PER"],[761,770,"ORG"],[774,780,"DAT"],[791,806,"PER"],[826,833,"DAT"],[858,863,"ORG"],[950,954,"DAT"],[955,972,"ORG"],[999,1006,"PER"],[1094,1099,"PER"],[1263,1273,"PER"],[1353,1373,"ORG"],[1447,1452,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":60,"text":"Arsenal have announced that goalkeeper Matt Turner has joined Nottingham Forest on a permanent transfer. The USMNT star only signed for Gunners last summer from MLS side New England Revolution, but his desire to play more regularly has seen him depart the Emirates Stadium after one season. With Arsenal agreeing a  £30m deal to sign David Raya from Brentford, Turner has now completed a move to the City Ground, signing a four year deal with Nottingham Forest. In a statement, Arsenal sporting director Edu said: \"On behalf of everyone at the club, we would like to thank Matt for his contribution to Arsenal and wish him and his family all the best in their new chapter. \"Matt is an international goalkeeper with the United States and is at a stage of his career when he needs to be playing regularly. He is leaving with our best wishes to join Nottingham Forest.\" feed In their unveiling at Nottingham Forest, Turner said: \"It feels great to be here. It's something I'm really looking forward to, it's a great challenge and a great step in my career. \"When I heard that there was interest to bring me here, it just felt right for my family, it felt right when my agent spoke to me about it and it feels like the right move for me right now. \"The manager and the backroom staff, everything about the club has a little sparkle to it. It's felt right from the start and I   m happy it's got done. \"I'm looking forward to making a connection with my teammates, the fans and the city. I'm grateful to be here and can't wait to get things started.\"","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[39,50,"PER"],[62,79,"ORG"],[109,114,"ORG"],[136,143,"ORG"],[161,164,"ORG"],[170,192,"ORG"],[256,272,"LOC"],[296,303,"ORG"],[316,320,"MON"],[334,344,"PER"],[350,359,"ORG"],[361,367,"PER"],[443,460,"ORG"],[478,485,"ORG"],[504,507,"PER"],[573,577,"PER"],[602,609,"ORG"],[674,678,"PER"],[715,732,"LOC"],[847,863,"ORG"],[894,911,"ORG"],[913,919,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":61,"text":"Arsenal will initially sign Brentford goalkeeper David Raya on a season-long loan with an option to then make the deal permanent in 2024, 90min understands. Raya has made it clear that he is ready to take the next step in his career, with Brentford repeatedly pointing suitors to a  £40m price tag. That figure put Tottenham and Bayern Munich off pursuing a deal, but Arsenal were able to come to a  £30m agreement earlier this week. It isn   t a straight transfer though. 90min understands that the agreement will actually see Raya sign a one-year extension to his Brentford contract so that it then expires in the summer of 2025 instead of at the end of this season     that could have seen him walk away as a free agent. He will then join Arsenal on loan for the duration of the 2023\/24 season, rather than outright. At the end of the loan, the Gunners will have an option to make it permanent for the total  £30m already agreed. It is not, however, an obligation to buy. feed That gives Arsenal a get out option should Raya not succeed in establishing himself. In the same breath, should the Spaniard end up returning to Brentford, his value is protected by the contract extension and they would still have the opportunity to command a sizeable transfer fee. The proposed structure of the deal will financially benefit Arsenal, who have already splashed out more than  £200m in transfer fees this summer on Kai Havertz, Jurrien Timber and Declan Rice. Hailing from Barcelona, Raya has spent his entire senior career in English football, having moved from Catalan club Cornella to Blackburn   s academy at the age of 16 almost a decade ago.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[28,37,"ORG"],[49,59,"PER"],[132,136,"DAT"],[138,143,"ORG"],[157,161,"PER"],[239,248,"ORG"],[283,287,"MON"],[315,324,"ORG"],[329,342,"ORG"],[368,375,"ORG"],[400,404,"MON"],[473,478,"ORG"],[528,532,"PER"],[566,575,"ORG"],[626,630,"DAT"],[742,749,"ORG"],[782,789,"DAT"],[844,855,"ORG"],[912,916,"MON"],[991,998,"ORG"],[1023,1027,"PER"],[1125,1134,"ORG"],[1323,1330,"ORG"],[1373,1378,"MON"],[1411,1422,"PER"],[1424,1438,"PER"],[1443,1454,"PER"],[1469,1478,"ORG"],[1480,1484,"PER"],[1567,1580,"ORG"],[1584,1593,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":62,"text":"Manchester United midfielder Fred is on course to join Fenerbahce after a deal was agreed with the Turkish Super Lig giants ahead of their fiercest rivals, 90min understands. Fred made 56 appearances for United last season, although he was primarily a back-up option and started only 12 times in the Premier League. The Brazilian has since also seen Mason Mount join the club, adding further competition for midfield places. It was the arrivals of both Christian Eriksen and Casemiro last summer that initially pushed him down the Old Trafford pecking order. Fulham had been interested in Fred, who joined United ahead of Manchester City from Shakhtar Donetsk for close to  £50m in the summer of 2018, but were not prepared to meet the asking price. feed Nottingham Forest were also in touch with the player   s representatives, but didn   t take things further, while Roma made an enquiry too. As 90min reported at the time, Galatasaray had an offer rejected in mid-July because it fell short of the  £20m asking price. Now, however, United have agreed to sell for less. The deal negotiated with Fenerbahce is worth  £13m (   15m), inclusive of add-ons. Fred also resisted the opportunity to move to the Saudi Pro League, which has already welcomed the likes of N   Golo Kante, Fabinho, Jordan Henderson and Ruben Neves from the Premier League this summer.","label":[[0,17,"ORG"],[29,33,"PER"],[55,65,"ORG"],[99,116,"ORG"],[156,161,"ORG"],[175,179,"PER"],[204,210,"ORG"],[300,314,"ORG"],[350,361,"PER"],[453,470,"PER"],[475,483,"PER"],[531,543,"LOC"],[559,565,"ORG"],[589,593,"PER"],[606,612,"ORG"],[622,637,"ORG"],[643,659,"ORG"],[674,678,"MON"],[696,700,"DAT"],[755,772,"ORG"],[869,873,"ORG"],[898,903,"ORG"],[926,937,"ORG"],[1002,1006,"MON"],[1035,1041,"ORG"],[1097,1107,"ORG"],[1118,1122,"MON"],[1127,1130,"MON"],[1201,1221,"ORG"],[1263,1277,"PER"],[1279,1286,"PER"],[1288,1304,"PER"],[1309,1320,"PER"],[1326,1344,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":63,"text":"Chelsea are expected to match Liverpool's bid for Brighton & Hove Albion midfielder Moises Caicedo, sources have confirmed to 90min. The Reds agreed to pay a British-record  £111m fee to the Seagulls during the early hours of Friday morning and had expected to wrap up a deal for the midfielder over the weekend. Liverpool were so confident that completion of Caicedo's move was imminent that manager Jurgen Klopp openly talked about negotiations during a press conference on Friday. Caicedo was due on Merseyside to undergo a medical soon after the conclusion of Klopp's presser, but has yet to arrive to complete the move to Liverpool and the club are believed to be furious at his representatives. 90min now understands that the Ecuador international has informed Brighton that he is prioritising a move to Chelsea and wants the club to allow further time to receive an acceptable offer. feed Chelsea saw bids worth  £70m and  £80m for Caicedo rejected by Brighton earlier this summer, despite being made aware that only offers north of  £100m would be considered, and sources have told 90min they will now match Liverpool's record sum in the next 24 hours in order to try and close a deal. 90min reported earlier on Friday that Chelsea were refusing to accept defeat in the race to sign Caicedo and it appears they may be given another chance to make their move for their top midfield target. Chelsea have since abandoned their pursuit of Leeds United's Tyler Adams despite agreeing a  £20m fee. Ironically, 90min understands that Brighton have been in touch with the USMNT captain's representatives regarding a move to the Amex Stadium.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[30,41,"ORG"],[50,58,"ORG"],[61,72,"ORG"],[84,98,"PER"],[126,131,"ORG"],[133,141,"ORG"],[174,179,"MON"],[187,199,"ORG"],[313,322,"ORG"],[360,369,"ORG"],[401,413,"PER"],[484,491,"PER"],[503,513,"LOC"],[564,571,"PER"],[627,636,"ORG"],[701,706,"ORG"],[767,775,"ORG"],[810,817,"ORG"],[896,903,"ORG"],[920,924,"MON"],[930,934,"MON"],[939,946,"PER"],[959,967,"ORG"],[1041,1046,"MON"],[1090,1095,"ORG"],[1116,1127,"ORG"],[1194,1199,"ORG"],[1232,1239,"ORG"],[1291,1298,"PER"],[1397,1404,"ORG"],[1443,1457,"ORG"],[1458,1469,"PER"],[1490,1494,"MON"],[1512,1517,"ORG"],[1535,1543,"ORG"],[1568,1577,"ORG"],[1624,1640,"LOC"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":64,"text":"West Ham United have finalised the signing of midfielder Edson Alvarez from Ajax. The Hammers have been exploring how to spend the  £105m earned by Declan Rice's sale to Arsenal and have begun their shopping spree with a move for Alvarez, who 90min understands will set West Ham back around  £34m if all add-ons are met. Alvarez, 25, has signed a five-year contract at London Stadium to become West Ham's first addition of the summer. \"I am very happy and very proud to be here,\" Alvarez told club media. \"Being here in London and seeing London Stadium, it   s amazing. I can   t wait to play here in front of the West Ham fans. \"It   s a hugely sentimental moment for me in my career. To join a club like a West Ham is a dream for me and my family.  \"The Premier League is a special league, the best league in the world and I think my style will suit it. I now have a responsibility to West Ham and the West Ham family and I will give absolutely everything for the shirt.\" feed Manager David Moyes added: \"We   re really pleased to add Edson to our squad. The midfield area was one we were especially keen to strengthen this summer     and Edson will complement the other options we have in that department. \"He   s an experienced international player, who has enjoyed great success for both club and country during his career to date.\" \"We   re excited about welcoming to West Ham and seeing him play his part in English and European competition for the Club.\" West Ham's spending may just be getting started after bids of  £30m for both Southampton's James Ward-Prowse and Manchester United's Harry Maguire were accepted.","label":[[0,15,"ORG"],[57,70,"PER"],[76,80,"ORG"],[82,93,"ORG"],[132,137,"MON"],[148,161,"PER"],[170,177,"ORG"],[230,237,"PER"],[243,248,"ORG"],[270,278,"ORG"],[292,296,"MON"],[321,328,"PER"],[369,383,"LOC"],[394,404,"ORG"],[480,487,"PER"],[520,526,"LOC"],[538,552,"LOC"],[614,622,"ORG"],[708,716,"ORG"],[752,770,"ORG"],[887,895,"ORG"],[904,912,"ORG"],[987,998,"PER"],[1037,1042,"PER"],[1141,1146,"PER"],[1374,1382,"ORG"],[1463,1473,"ORG"],[1526,1530,"MON"],[1540,1553,"ORG"],[1554,1571,"PER"],[1576,1595,"ORG"],[1596,1609,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":65,"text":"Real Madrid have sold home-grown attacker Sergio Arribas to fellow La Liga club Almeria. Arribas joined Madrid from the youth system at city neighbours Leganes back in 2012 and gradually rose through the ranks at Valdebebas. The forward made his first-team debut in September 2020 and had played eight senior games by the end of that campaign, combining duties with Real Madrid Castilla. Arribas spent the entirety of 2021\/22 with the reserve team, before reappearing for the first-team in 2022\/23. He even scored his first goal in the FIFA Club World Cup against Al Ahly of Egypt. With Real Madrid Castilla last season, Arribas scored 18 goals in 34 appearances. Madrid are yet to replace Karim Benzema and have also let Mariano Diaz leave, but 21-year-old Arribas won   t be used to plug the attacking holes in the squad. He has now signed a long-term contract with Almeria until the summer of 2029. In their first top flight campaign since 2015, Almeria narrowly avoided relegation last season.","label":[[0,11,"ORG"],[42,56,"PER"],[67,74,"ORG"],[80,87,"ORG"],[89,96,"PER"],[104,110,"ORG"],[152,159,"ORG"],[168,172,"DAT"],[213,223,"LOC"],[266,280,"DAT"],[366,386,"ORG"],[388,395,"PER"],[418,425,"DAT"],[490,497,"DAT"],[532,555,"ORG"],[564,571,"ORG"],[575,580,"LOC"],[587,607,"ORG"],[621,628,"PER"],[664,670,"ORG"],[690,703,"PER"],[722,734,"PER"],[758,765,"PER"],[868,875,"ORG"],[886,900,"DAT"],[943,947,"DAT"],[949,956,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":66,"text":"Juventus' training match against Juventus Next Gen was interrupted on Wednesday by a pitch invasion which saw supporters protest a possible move for Chelsea striker Romelu Lukaku. The clubs have spoken this summer about a possible deal for Lukaku which would also see Dusan Vlahovic head to Stamford Bridge, but while Chelsea appreciate the Serbian striker, 90min understands they have a huge issue with Juve's demand for an extra  £35m as part of the deal. These negotiations came after Lukaku's proposed return to Inter collapsed when the Italian side learned of talks between Juventus and the Belgian, who had privately and publicly vowed never to play for any Serie A side other than Inter. As a result, Lukaku's proposed move to the Allianz Stadium has not gone down well among fans, many of whom were heard screaming \"No, we don't want Lukaku\" during Wednesday's friendly - chants which initially began in the stands during the first minute of the game. It's worth noting that this game between Juventus and Juventus Next Gen took the place of the annual Villar Perosa friendly, in which it is tradition for fans to invade the pitch. But while the event is usually full of positivity as fans get the chance to meet players, a large number of supporters chose to use the opportunity to oppose a move for Lukaku instead. Invasione (anche senza Villar Perosa) #Juve pic.twitter.com\/zpGsQcm7Ko Sources have confirmed to 90min that Chelsea are no longer entertaining the idea of a swap deal between Lukaku and Vlahovic as they do not share Juventus' valuation of the latter, but the Blues are still open to a straight sale if the right bid arrives for Lukaku. Options for Lukaku, who rejected an approach from Saudi Arabia earlier this summer, are proving limited after Inter closed the door on a potential transfer. \"Given what Inter has done for him, we expected him to behave differently, as a professional and as a man,\" Inter vice-president Javier Zanetti told La Gazzetta dello Sport. \"He has the right to go where he wants, of course, but he could have told us that beforehand. Nobody is bigger than the club and when building a team, you always have to consider who you are bringing into the dressing room.\"","label":[[0,8,"ORG"],[33,50,"ORG"],[149,156,"ORG"],[165,178,"PER"],[240,246,"PER"],[268,282,"PER"],[291,306,"ORG"],[318,325,"ORG"],[358,363,"ORG"],[404,410,"ORG"],[432,436,"MON"],[488,496,"PER"],[541,548,"LOC"],[579,587,"ORG"],[596,603,"LOC"],[664,671,"ORG"],[688,693,"ORG"],[708,716,"PER"],[734,753,"LOC"],[842,848,"PER"],[1001,1009,"ORG"],[1014,1031,"ORG"],[1061,1074,"ORG"],[1309,1315,"PER"],[1422,1427,"ORG"],[1433,1440,"ORG"],[1500,1506,"PER"],[1511,1519,"PER"],[1541,1549,"ORG"],[1580,1589,"ORG"],[1653,1659,"PER"],[1673,1679,"PER"],[1711,1723,"LOC"],[1830,1835,"ORG"],[1926,1931,"ORG"],[1947,1961,"PER"],[1967,1990,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":67,"text":"Kylian Mbappe has reiterated his desire to stay with Paris Saint-Germain and see out the remainder of his contract in the French capital, 90min understands. The 24-year-old shocked PSG earlier this summer when he told them he would not be exercising the option to extend his contract, which is set to expire in June next year. PSG have responded by trying to sell Mbappe this summer, in a desperate bid to avoid losing one of the world's best players on a free transfer, but he has made it clear on numerous occasions that he intends to leave next year as a free agent. The Ligue 1 giants even accepted a world record offer of  £257m (   300m) from Al Hilal last month, but despite putting forward a gargantuan contract offer to Mbappe, the PIF-backed Saudi Pro League side were unable to persuade the World Cup Golden Boot winner to enter negotiations. Chelsea have also been contracted by PSG in a bid to drum up further interest in Mbappe, as have a number of other heavyweight European clubs. Mbappe was left out of PSG's recent pre-season tour of Japan and has been banished from first-team duties as the dispute between player and club rages on - sources have told 90min that club president Nasser Al-Khelaifi has even warned Fayza Lamari, his mother and agent, that Mbappe will 'not put a PSG shirt on again.' manual Despite the hostile atmopshere, Mbappe's position on the matter remains unchanged. 90min understands that he intends to spend the next 12 months in Paris before moving on to his next venture, which many believe will be at Real Madrid, and he has informed PSG of his plan. Sources close to Mbappe and Real Madrid have vehemently denied that an agreement is already in place for him to move to the Spanish capital next summer, but he came within a whisker of joining Madrid in 2022 before a last-minute change of heart saw him sign a new contract at PSG. Mbappe's sidelining is part of a radical overhaul at PSG this summer. Lionel Messi has already departed for Inter Miami, while the Parisiens are also keen to ship out Neymar. He has interest in his services from Saudi Arabia, with a potential return to Barcelona also rumoured in recent weeks.","label":[[0,13,"PER"],[53,72,"ORG"],[122,128,"ORG"],[138,143,"ORG"],[181,184,"ORG"],[311,315,"DAT"],[327,330,"ORG"],[364,370,"PER"],[574,581,"ORG"],[628,633,"MON"],[638,642,"MON"],[649,657,"ORG"],[729,735,"PER"],[741,744,"ORG"],[752,768,"ORG"],[798,811,"ORG"],[854,861,"ORG"],[891,894,"ORG"],[935,941,"PER"],[997,1003,"PER"],[1020,1025,"ORG"],[1052,1057,"LOC"],[1171,1176,"ORG"],[1197,1215,"PER"],[1232,1244,"PER"],[1273,1279,"PER"],[1296,1299,"ORG"],[1356,1364,"PER"],[1407,1412,"ORG"],[1472,1477,"LOC"],[1546,1558,"ORG"],[1579,1582,"ORG"],[1613,1619,"PER"],[1624,1635,"ORG"],[1720,1727,"ORG"],[1789,1795,"ORG"],[1799,1803,"DAT"],[1872,1875,"ORG"],[1877,1885,"PER"],[1930,1933,"ORG"],[1947,1959,"PER"],[1985,1996,"ORG"],[2044,2050,"PER"],[2089,2101,"LOC"],[2130,2139,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":68,"text":"Barcelona are not concerned about losing midfielder Ilkay Gundogan over a registration clause in his contract, 90min understands. Gundogan joined on a free transfer from Manchester City this summer, inking a two-year contract which also includes an option for the midfielder to terminate his deal if he is not registered in Barcelona's squad by the time the new La Liga season kicks off this weekend. Financial restrictions mean Barcelona have not yet registered any of their new singings - Gundogan, Oriol Romeu, Inigo Martinez - as well as any new contracts agreed this summer and the return of loanees like Ez Abde and Fermin Lopez.  As it stands, manager Xavi has just 13 eligible players for the season-opener against Getafe on 13 August, including Ousmane Dembele and Franck Kessie, who are on the cusp of leaving the club. The imminent sales of Dembele and Kessie, to Paris Saint-Germain and Al Ahli respectively, are expected to net Barcelona around    65m ( £56m), while talks are also on over a 16% sale of Barca Studios which would provide another cash injection. feed Sources have confirmed to 90min that Barcelona are confident they will wrap up their outstanding deals in time to register Gundogan and the rest of their new signings before the new season gets underway. As was the case with Gavi earlier this summer when the midfielder's contract extension was delayed, Gundogan is not causing problems behind the scene and is not contemplating an early exit from Camp Nou. While Barcelona understand their current situation, sources close to the club insist they are confident they have the financial capacity to register all their new signings - a stance exemplified by ongoing efforts to sign Manchester City duo Bernardo Silva and Joao Cancelo. Gundogan and the rest of Barcelona's new signings can be registered up to and including the day of the Getafe game, and club officials are optimistic everything will be finalised in time.","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[52,66,"PER"],[111,116,"ORG"],[130,138,"PER"],[170,185,"ORG"],[324,335,"ORG"],[362,369,"ORG"],[429,438,"ORG"],[491,499,"PER"],[501,512,"PER"],[514,528,"PER"],[610,617,"PER"],[622,634,"PER"],[659,663,"PER"],[723,729,"ORG"],[733,742,"DAT"],[754,769,"PER"],[774,787,"PER"],[852,859,"PER"],[864,870,"PER"],[875,894,"ORG"],[899,906,"ORG"],[941,950,"ORG"],[961,964,"MON"],[967,971,"MON"],[1005,1008,"PCT"],[1017,1030,"ORG"],[1106,1111,"ORG"],[1117,1126,"ORG"],[1203,1211,"PER"],[1305,1309,"PER"],[1384,1392,"PER"],[1478,1486,"LOC"],[1494,1503,"ORG"],[1710,1725,"ORG"],[1730,1744,"PER"],[1749,1761,"PER"],[1763,1771,"PER"],[1788,1799,"ORG"],[1866,1872,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":69,"text":"Arsenal have rejected a  £30m bid from Ligue 1 side Monaco for Folarin Balogun, sources have confirmed to 90min. Balogun returned to the Gunners during the summer after a successful loan spell with Reims in which the forward managed a stunning 21 goals in Ligue 1 for the mid-table team. Despite expectations being high among Gunners fans upon his return to the Emirates, the striker barely featured during a pre-season riddled with injury concerns. Even without a dismal pre-season with Arsenal, Balogun has long been expected to leave the club once again this summer but this time permanently - the player himself stated in June that he \"definitely\" would not go out on loan again. The USMNT international has also consistently rejected the opportunity to enter talks over a new contract at the Emirates Stadium due to the lack of guarantees of game time.  90min reported in July that this resistance to signing a new deal, and unwillingness to go out on loan, has led to Arsenal slapping a  £50m price tag on the striker. feed Crystal Palace, West Ham United, Brentford, Fulham and UEFA Champions League finalists Inter have all been in contact regarding the player's services, but sources have now confirmed to 90min that Monaco are the first to table an offer.  The Ligue 1 club have made an opening bid of  £30m which has been swiftly reject by the Gunners, who are holding firm on their  £50m price tag.  Monaco have stepped up their efforts to sign a new striker following Breel Embolo's ACL injury during a pre-season game. The ailment will see the Swiss forward miss the bulk of the 2023\/24 campaign, making the signing of a new starting calibre striker a priority for the principality club.  Along with Balogun, 90min understands that Gift Orban of Gent and reported Chelsea and West Ham target Elye Wahi have also been shortlisted by Monaco. Both forwards have recently held talks with representatives of Tottenham Hotspur.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[25,29,"MON"],[39,46,"ORG"],[52,58,"LOC"],[63,78,"PER"],[106,111,"ORG"],[113,120,"PER"],[133,144,"ORG"],[198,203,"ORG"],[256,263,"ORG"],[326,333,"ORG"],[358,370,"ORG"],[488,495,"ORG"],[497,504,"PER"],[684,693,"ORG"],[793,813,"LOC"],[859,864,"ORG"],[877,881,"DAT"],[974,981,"ORG"],[994,998,"MON"],[1030,1044,"ORG"],[1046,1061,"ORG"],[1063,1072,"ORG"],[1074,1080,"ORG"],[1085,1106,"ORG"],[1117,1122,"ORG"],[1215,1220,"ORG"],[1226,1232,"LOC"],[1271,1278,"ORG"],[1313,1317,"MON"],[1351,1362,"ORG"],[1395,1399,"MON"],[1412,1418,"LOC"],[1481,1495,"PER"],[1558,1563,"ORG"],[1593,1600,"DAT"],[1714,1721,"PER"],[1723,1728,"ORG"],[1746,1756,"PER"],[1760,1764,"ORG"],[1778,1785,"ORG"],[1790,1798,"ORG"],[1806,1815,"PER"],[1846,1852,"LOC"],[1917,1934,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":70,"text":"Liverpool have agreed a British record deal worth  £111m to sign Brighton midfielder Moises Caicedo, 90min understands. The Reds opened talks with Brighton on Thursday as they pivoted from Southampton's Romeo Lavia to Caicedo and now terms are agreed between the two clubs. Caicedo had been Chelsea's prime midfield target all summer, but they baulked at the idea of meeting Brighton's value - which has always been at least  £100m - while Liverpool's offer of  £111m was immediately accepted. Such a deal would represent a British record, eclipsing the  £106m Chelsea paid to land Enzo Fernandez in January. Chelsea made numerous offers for Caicedo, but their highest did not exceed  £80m and now they have missed out on the Ecuador star who is destined for Anfield, where he will help form an overhauled midfield containing Hungarian star Dominik Szoboszlai and former Seagulls teammate Alexis Mac Allister. feed Caicedo is now due to head to Merseyside to complete his medical and is expected to sign his contract before this weekend's Premier League opener, which just so happens to come against Chelsea at Stamford Bridge on Sunday. For Liverpool, the deal is an obvious club record, eclipsing the  £75m paid to sign centre-back Virgil van Dijk from Southampton in January 2018. While such an expensive move was not initially on the cards this summer, Liverpool raised significant funds through the unplanned sales of Jordan Henderson and Fabinho to Saudi Arabia and ultimately decided to pull the trigger. As for Chelsea, the Blues joined the bidding for Liverpool target Lavia earlier this week as they submitted a  £48m offer for the Southampton midfielder, who has been valued at  £50m. Chelsea have also confirmed their intention to trigger the  £20m release clause of Leeds United midfielder Tyler Adams.","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[51,56,"MON"],[65,73,"ORG"],[85,99,"PER"],[101,106,"ORG"],[120,128,"ORG"],[147,155,"ORG"],[189,202,"ORG"],[203,214,"PER"],[218,225,"PER"],[274,281,"PER"],[291,300,"ORG"],[375,385,"ORG"],[426,431,"MON"],[440,451,"ORG"],[462,467,"MON"],[555,560,"MON"],[561,568,"ORG"],[582,596,"PER"],[600,607,"DAT"],[609,616,"ORG"],[642,649,"ORG"],[685,689,"MON"],[726,733,"LOC"],[759,766,"LOC"],[841,859,"PER"],[871,879,"ORG"],[889,908,"PER"],[915,922,"PER"],[945,955,"LOC"],[1039,1053,"ORG"],[1100,1107,"ORG"],[1111,1126,"LOC"],[1142,1151,"ORG"],[1204,1208,"MON"],[1234,1249,"PER"],[1255,1266,"ORG"],[1270,1282,"DAT"],[1357,1366,"ORG"],[1423,1439,"PER"],[1444,1451,"PER"],[1455,1467,"LOC"],[1519,1526,"ORG"],[1528,1537,"ORG"],[1561,1570,"ORG"],[1578,1583,"PER"],[1623,1627,"MON"],[1642,1653,"ORG"],[1690,1694,"MON"],[1696,1703,"ORG"],[1756,1760,"MON"],[1779,1791,"ORG"],[1803,1814,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":71,"text":"Bayern Munich are continuing to scour the goalkeeper market and are now keeping tabs on Spanish duo Kepa Arrizabalaga and David de Gea, sources have confirmed to 90min. The German champions have been looking to add another stopper to their ranks while Manuel Neuer continues his recovery from a broken leg that he suffered during a skiing trip back in December. They had previously looked at Brentford's David Raya, but like Tottenham Hotspur refused to match the  £40m valuation. The Bees have since agreed to sell him to Arsenal for  £30m. With Yann Sommer signing for Inter in recent days, Bayern are stepping up their pursuit of a new goalkeeper. 90min understands they have made an enquiry to Chelsea regarding Kepa. feed The Blues are open to selling their current number one, who has two years left to run on his contract at Stamford Bridge, but Bayern's interest has not gone beyond this initial enquiry. Chelsea have brought in a goalkeeper of their own this transfer window, signing Robert Sanchez from Brighton for a fee in the region of  £20m. 90min understands that Bayern are also considering making a contract offer to free agent De Gea, who has been without a club since July after leaving Manchester United. De Gea also has suitors in the Saudi Pro League and it remains to be seen whether he would turn down such lucrative offers to join Bayern as a backup. Other goalkeepers on Bayern's shortlist include Porto's Diogo Costa and Valencia's Giorgi Mamardashvili, who have both been monitored by Premier League clubs in the past year.","label":[[0,13,"ORG"],[100,117,"PER"],[122,134,"PER"],[162,167,"ORG"],[252,264,"PER"],[392,403,"ORG"],[404,414,"PER"],[425,442,"ORG"],[465,469,"MON"],[481,489,"ORG"],[523,530,"ORG"],[536,540,"MON"],[547,558,"PER"],[571,576,"ORG"],[593,599,"ORG"],[651,656,"ORG"],[698,705,"ORG"],[716,720,"PER"],[727,736,"ORG"],[832,847,"LOC"],[853,861,"ORG"],[913,920,"ORG"],[993,1007,"PER"],[1013,1021,"ORG"],[1050,1054,"MON"],[1056,1061,"ORG"],[1079,1085,"ORG"],[1145,1151,"PER"],[1187,1191,"DAT"],[1206,1223,"ORG"],[1225,1231,"PER"],[1256,1272,"ORG"],[1356,1362,"ORG"],[1397,1405,"ORG"],[1424,1431,"ORG"],[1432,1443,"PER"],[1448,1458,"ORG"],[1459,1479,"PER"],[1513,1527,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":72,"text":"Japanese goalkeeper Zion Suzuki has confirmed he turned down a move to Manchester United this summer amid concerns over the minutes available to him. After David de Gea's departure on a free transfer, United began looking for two new goalkeepers and were reported to have lined up 20-year-old Suzuki, then of Japanese side Urawa Red Diamonds, as a possible backup to new number one Andre Onana. Suzuki had other plans, however, taking his talents to Belgium and joining Sint-Truiden on loan with a view to a permanent transfer next summer. While Suzuki admitted he would love to play for United in future, he confessed that he did not want to sit on the bench behind  £47.2m signing Onana. feed \"I decided to transfer this time as a step up in aiming to be the best in the world. It's true that there was an offer from Manchester United,\" Suzuki told the media. \"As a football player and as a person, if I hadn't thought about anything, of course, I would like to go to Manchester United, but among them, I really want to spend time thinking about what kind of future awaits me. After much thought, I made this decision. \"Manchester United have acquired Onana. It's important for me to participate in matches, and I think it is also important to play on the world stage. I want to make the most of what I have learned here and do my best.\" Despite his initial rejection, Suzuki confirmed he dreams of making the move to the Premier League and flying the flag for his country. \"While many players are active overseas, it is difficult to become a keeper,\" he concluded. \"I think we are going to have a really tough battle ahead of us in that position. \"There are still no Japanese who are active as goalkeepers in the Premier League, so I want to be one of the first players to do so. I want to keep moving forward step by step.\"","label":[[20,31,"PER"],[71,88,"ORG"],[156,170,"PER"],[201,207,"ORG"],[293,299,"PER"],[323,341,"ORG"],[382,393,"PER"],[395,401,"PER"],[450,457,"LOC"],[470,482,"ORG"],[546,552,"PER"],[588,594,"ORG"],[668,674,"MON"],[683,688,"PER"],[819,836,"ORG"],[839,845,"PER"],[970,987,"ORG"],[1122,1139,"ORG"],[1154,1159,"PER"],[1371,1377,"PER"],[1420,1438,"ORG"],[1712,1730,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":73,"text":"Tottenham Hotspur are exploring opportunities to sign a new forward despite their insistence that Harry Kane will not be sold this summer, sources have confirmed to 90min. Bayern Munich have had three bids for Kane knocked back by Spurs already this transfer window and are preparing a fourth worth  £94.6m (   110m). However, 90min understands that Tottenham have showed no indication that this will be enough to convince them to sell their star striker, who has less than a year left to run on his contract. 90min revealed on Tuesday that Kane would like his future sorted before the start of the new Premier League campaign - if he is still at Tottenham by the time they face Brentford on Sunday, he is happy to stay put for the entirety of 2023\/24. Tottenham remain hopeful they can convince Kane to commit his long-term future to the club and he has been impressed by new head coach Ange Postecoglou following his appointment in June. Though Spurs are adamant that Kane will not be allowed to leave, they have brought in a new centre forward in Argentina youth international Alejo Veliz this week and could yet sign another this summer. feed Sources have told 90min that representatives of Spurs have sounded out several other strikers regarding potential moves to north London. 21-year-old Gent forward Gift Orban, who has scored a staggering 22 goals in 24 games since joining the Belgian club last year, is one target that Tottenham have spoken to. Chelsea target Elye Wahi of Montpellier and Lille star Jonathan David are also on Spurs' radar, as is wantaway Fulham talisman Aleksandar Mitrovic, who saw a proposed move to Saudi Pro League side Al Hilal fall through earlier this summer. Mitrovic was keen on a move to Saudi Arabia but Al Hilal failed to stump up more than  £30m, with Fulham demanding closer to  £50m for the Serbia international. Beyond Kane and Veliz, Brazil's starting number nine Richarlison is also on Tottenham's books and has enjoyed a fruitful pre-season under Postecoglou.","label":[[0,17,"ORG"],[98,108,"PER"],[165,170,"ORG"],[172,185,"ORG"],[210,214,"PER"],[231,236,"ORG"],[300,306,"MON"],[311,315,"MON"],[327,332,"ORG"],[350,359,"ORG"],[510,515,"ORG"],[541,545,"PER"],[603,617,"ORG"],[647,656,"ORG"],[679,688,"ORG"],[744,751,"DAT"],[753,762,"ORG"],[796,800,"PER"],[888,904,"PER"],[934,938,"DAT"],[947,952,"ORG"],[970,974,"PER"],[1050,1059,"LOC"],[1080,1091,"PER"],[1165,1170,"ORG"],[1195,1200,"ORG"],[1270,1282,"LOC"],[1296,1300,"ORG"],[1309,1319,"PER"],[1431,1440,"ORG"],[1457,1464,"ORG"],[1472,1481,"PER"],[1485,1496,"LOC"],[1501,1506,"LOC"],[1512,1526,"PER"],[1539,1544,"ORG"],[1568,1574,"ORG"],[1584,1603,"PER"],[1632,1648,"ORG"],[1654,1662,"ORG"],[1697,1705,"PER"],[1728,1740,"LOC"],[1745,1753,"ORG"],[1784,1788,"MON"],[1795,1801,"ORG"],[1823,1827,"MON"],[1865,1869,"PER"],[1874,1879,"PER"],[1881,1889,"ORG"],[1911,1922,"PER"],[1934,1945,"ORG"],[1996,2007,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":74,"text":"Brighton CEO Paul Barber says the club hopes to hold onto Chelsea target Moises Caicedo and \"understands\" the current interest in the Ecuador international. Caicedo has become one of the best midfielders in the Premier League during his time at the AMEX and attracted interest from both the Blues and Arsenal during the January transfer window. The midfielder asked to leave but Brighton stood firm and have maintained their not-for-sale stance during the summer so far. The youngster is said to have skipped training recently in a bid to force through a move to Stamford Bridge and wasn't involved in Brighton's final pre-season friendly of the summer against Rayo Vallecano. 90min understands Brighton have told Caicedo they will not sell him unless their  £100m valuation is met. Chelsea are still chasing the 21-year-old and Barber insisted the south coast side do not want him to leave this year. feed He said: \"For a young player like Moises at 21, he's probably one of the best midfield players in the world already at his age, and we've had a fantastic time working with him. And we want it to continue, we've got him under a long contract. \"We're also realistic to know there is interest in him. As a young man, that interest is inevitably going to have an impact on your thought process and unsettle you a little bit. We understand that. \"But for now, he's a Brighton player, he's under contract. We expect him to work hard, prepare for the new season and we'll see what happens as the window goes on. \"The window's got a long way to go, we'd love to keep him. He's a really important player, we'll see where we are.\" Brighton lost Leandro Trossard to Arsenal in January and have also sold Alexis Mac Allister and Robert Sanchez to Liverpool and Chelsea this window respectively. However, they have responded with incoming deals for Joao Pedro, Mahmoud Dahoud, James Milner, Bart Verbruggen and Igor Julio. A club-record  £34.5m deal has also been agreed with Ajax for Ghana forward Mohammed Kudus, though an agreement over personal terms still hasn't been reached.","label":[[0,8,"ORG"],[13,24,"PER"],[58,65,"ORG"],[73,87,"PER"],[134,141,"ORG"],[157,164,"PER"],[211,225,"ORG"],[245,253,"LOC"],[287,296,"ORG"],[301,308,"ORG"],[320,327,"DAT"],[379,387,"ORG"],[563,578,"LOC"],[602,612,"ORG"],[661,675,"ORG"],[677,682,"ORG"],[695,703,"ORG"],[714,721,"PER"],[759,764,"MON"],[783,790,"ORG"],[829,835,"PER"],[941,947,"PER"],[1369,1377,"ORG"],[1628,1636,"ORG"],[1642,1658,"PER"],[1662,1669,"ORG"],[1673,1680,"DAT"],[1700,1719,"PER"],[1724,1738,"PER"],[1742,1751,"ORG"],[1756,1763,"ORG"],[1843,1853,"PER"],[1855,1869,"PER"],[1871,1883,"PER"],[1885,1900,"PER"],[1905,1915,"PER"],[1932,1938,"MON"],[1970,1974,"ORG"],[1979,1984,"LOC"],[1993,2007,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":75,"text":"Barcelona manager Xavi has responded to rumours linking Neymar with a sensational return to Catalonia this summer.  The Brazilian superstar has been heavily linked with a move away from current club Paris Saint-Germain, with 90min recently revealing that the Ligue 1 giants are working hard to try and move the forward on.  Signed for a world record fee of  £190m (   222m) back in 2017, Neymar has largely disappointed during his time in Ligue 1 due to a myriad of injury concerns. The 31-year-old has never played more than 22 league games in any given season during his six year spell in Paris, and has failed to win the club their first ever UEFA Champions League - being on the losing end in the 2020 final.  Neymar enjoyed a much more successful stint at Barca between 2013 and 2017, winning the Champions League and two La Liga titles as an integral member of the famed 'MSN' frontline.  In light of PSG's interest in selling the player, Neymar has inevitably been linked with a return to his former club Barcelona. 90min understands that club president Joan Laporta is keen to re-sign Neymar, however manager Xavi would prefer if the club targeted Manchester City star Bernardo Silva.  feed Speaking to the press after Barcelona's 4-2 win over Tottenham Hotspur in the Joan Gamper Trophy on Tuesday evening, Xavi was asked about the links with Neymar, saying: \"I cannot say anything more about Neymar. Last year I had mentioned a name of a player from another team and that club got angry. From here until the end of the market, we will see.\" Xavi also commented on the need for Barca to bulk their squad further this summer, telling reporters: \"We have to strengthen ourselves well. The sports area and the president know this reality. I'm happy with how our players are training and our pre-season.\" Barcelona are likely to face stiff competition from PIF owned Saudi Pro League clubs and potentially Newcastle United, depending on the future direction the club's owners in regards to transfer policy.","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[18,22,"PER"],[56,62,"PER"],[92,101,"LOC"],[120,129,"ORG"],[199,218,"ORG"],[225,230,"ORG"],[259,266,"ORG"],[358,363,"MON"],[368,372,"MON"],[382,386,"DAT"],[388,394,"PER"],[439,446,"ORG"],[591,596,"LOC"],[646,667,"ORG"],[701,705,"DAT"],[714,720,"PER"],[761,766,"ORG"],[775,779,"DAT"],[784,788,"DAT"],[798,818,"ORG"],[827,834,"ORG"],[907,912,"ORG"],[945,951,"PER"],[1012,1021,"ORG"],[1023,1028,"ORG"],[1061,1073,"PER"],[1093,1099,"PER"],[1117,1121,"PER"],[1156,1171,"ORG"],[1177,1191,"PER"],[1227,1238,"ORG"],[1252,1269,"ORG"],[1277,1295,"ORG"],[1316,1320,"PER"],[1352,1358,"PER"],[1402,1408,"PER"],[1551,1555,"PER"],[1587,1592,"ORG"],[1810,1819,"ORG"],[1862,1865,"ORG"],[1872,1888,"ORG"],[1911,1927,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":76,"text":"Chelsea have launched a bid worth  £48m for Southampton's in-demand midfielder Romeo Lavia, sources have confirmed to 90min. The Blues are looking to bring in a couple of midfielders this month to bolster Mauricio Pochettino's options and Lavia has emerged as one of their prime targets. Chelsea are already in talks with Brighton & Hove Albion over Moises Caicedo and have seen a number of bids for him rejected, but 90min understands that, while those talks are continuing, they have now also made a move for Lavia. Chelsea have long been interested in Lavia, with their interest driven by their co-director of recruitment and talent Joe Shields - the man who took Lavia to Southampton in 2023. feed Southampton, who have agreed to sell their captain James Ward-Prowse to West Ham Untied for  £30m, are demanding  £50m for Belgian starlet Lavia and Chelsea's offer is short of that at  £48m, but it is the largest bid they have received so far this summer. Liverpool have been in pole position for Lavia, but they have seen three bids for the teenager rejected, with their latest offer for the 19-year-old being worth  £45m. Sources believe that Southampton are now more than confident that their  £50m asking price will be met by one of Lavia's suitors and they won't be accepting less.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[35,39,"MON"],[44,57,"ORG"],[79,90,"PER"],[118,123,"ORG"],[125,134,"ORG"],[205,226,"PER"],[239,244,"PER"],[288,295,"ORG"],[322,330,"ORG"],[333,344,"ORG"],[350,364,"ORG"],[418,423,"ORG"],[511,516,"PER"],[518,525,"ORG"],[555,560,"PER"],[636,647,"PER"],[667,672,"PER"],[676,687,"ORG"],[691,695,"DAT"],[702,713,"ORG"],[753,770,"PER"],[774,789,"ORG"],[795,799,"MON"],[816,820,"MON"],[841,846,"PER"],[851,860,"ORG"],[888,892,"MON"],[959,968,"ORG"],[1000,1005,"PER"],[1121,1125,"MON"],[1148,1159,"ORG"],[1200,1204,"MON"],[1240,1247,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":77,"text":"90min rounds up the latest  Real Madrid transfer news, rumours and gossip circulating around the world... Kylian Mbappe has been warned that he won't play a single minute for Paris Saint-Germain this season if he refuses to leave the club, by order of the Qatari owners. PSG have accepted offers from Al Hilal and an un-named Premeir League side, but Mbappe hasn't agreed to either. (Bruno Andrade) Real Madrid media staff are already preparing videos and online content for a potential Mbappe unveiling. Although it appears to be just in case, given that they did they same thing last and the board maintains there is still no chance he arrives this summer. (Rodra) Mbappe rejected PSG's second attempt to include a guaranteed selling clause in a proposed contract renewal with the Frenchman. (ESPN) Chelsea could rival Madrid in pursuit of Juventus striker Dusan Vlahovic, an option instead of Mbappe, after losing new arrival Christopher Nkunku to long-term injury. (ESPN) feed Alvaro Rodriguez is set to stay at Real Madrid this season, depsite being overlooked for the first-team's pre-season tour. Alaves and Espanyol have each enquired about loaning the 19-year-old, only to be met with rejection. (Mundo Deportivo) Yet to join a new club since he was let go by Madrid in June, Eden Hazard has been linked with a potential fresh start in MLS. Vancouver Whitecaps are rumoured to be keen on the Belgian, although there is also interest from historic Brazilian side Botafogo. (AS)","label":[[0,5,"ORG"],[28,39,"ORG"],[106,119,"PER"],[175,194,"ORG"],[271,274,"ORG"],[301,309,"ORG"],[326,340,"ORG"],[351,357,"PER"],[384,397,"PER"],[399,410,"ORG"],[487,493,"PER"],[660,665,"PER"],[667,673,"PER"],[683,688,"ORG"],[795,799,"ORG"],[801,808,"ORG"],[821,827,"ORG"],[842,850,"ORG"],[859,873,"PER"],[896,902,"PER"],[929,947,"PER"],[970,974,"ORG"],[981,997,"PER"],[1016,1027,"ORG"],[1104,1110,"ORG"],[1115,1123,"ORG"],[1206,1221,"ORG"],[1269,1275,"ORG"],[1279,1283,"DAT"],[1285,1296,"PER"],[1345,1348,"ORG"],[1350,1369,"ORG"],[1471,1479,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":78,"text":"Real Madrid are preparing to move for Sevilla goalkeeper Yassine Bounou, 90min understands, as they look to cover the long-term absence of Thibaut Courtois. The Belgian suffered an ACL injury during a training session earlier this week and will soon undergo surgery, which will keep him on the sidelines for the vast majority of the 2023\/24 La Liga season. With Ukraine international Andriy Lunin the only other goalkeeper in Carlo Ancelotti's squad, Madrid are prepared to enter the transfer market for a new stopper and have identified a number of potential targets. Contact has been made with former Manchester United goalkeeper David de Gea, while Chelsea's Kepa Arrizabalaga is also seen as a candidate for a loan move, but sources have confirmed to 90min that Bounou is at the top of Madrid's wish list. 32-year-old Bounou, who excelled with Morocco at the World Cup, has made 157 appearances in La Liga across his career, emerging as one of the division's most-reliable stoppers since his switch to Sevilla in 2020. feed 90min understands that Bounou has made it clear he would like the chance to move to Madrid and Sevilla are prepared to do business for a fee of around    20m ( £17.3m). Madrid were not planning to do any additional business after an expensive shopping spree which brought Jude Bellingham, Arda Guler, Fran Garcia and Joselu to the club, but Courtois' serious injury has forced them back into the market. While club officials are understood to be fans of Lunin, there is a desire to bring in a goalkeeper with more La Liga experience as Ancelotti seeks to wrestle the league title back from rivals Barcelona. Defence was a real issue for Ancelotti during pre-season, with the Spanish side conceding eight goals across four games, and the injury to Courtois has only complicated his attempted solution.","label":[[0,11,"ORG"],[38,45,"ORG"],[57,71,"PER"],[73,78,"ORG"],[139,155,"PER"],[333,340,"DAT"],[341,348,"ORG"],[362,369,"ORG"],[384,396,"PER"],[426,443,"PER"],[451,457,"ORG"],[603,620,"ORG"],[632,644,"PER"],[652,661,"ORG"],[662,679,"PER"],[755,760,"ORG"],[766,772,"PER"],[790,798,"ORG"],[822,828,"PER"],[848,855,"LOC"],[859,872,"ORG"],[902,909,"ORG"],[1006,1013,"ORG"],[1017,1021,"DAT"],[1028,1033,"ORG"],[1051,1057,"PER"],[1112,1118,"ORG"],[1123,1130,"ORG"],[1182,1185,"MON"],[1188,1194,"MON"],[1197,1203,"ORG"],[1300,1315,"PER"],[1317,1327,"PER"],[1329,1340,"PER"],[1345,1351,"PER"],[1369,1377,"PER"],[1482,1487,"PER"],[1542,1549,"ORG"],[1564,1573,"PER"],[1625,1634,"ORG"],[1665,1674,"PER"],[1775,1783,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":79,"text":"Manchester City believe they have convinced both Bernardo Silva and Kyle Walker to stay at the club and sign new contracts, sources have confirmed to 90min. Both players have been considering their futures this summer and had been looking to leave the treble-winners during the transfer window. However, after allowing Riyad Mahrez to join Ilkay Gundogan out the exit door, Man City boss Pep Guardiola and the club's hierarchy have been firm with their stance that Silva and Walker must not be sold as well. 90min revealed earlier this summer that Walker, like Mahrez, was left furious at missing out on the Champions League final and had been looking at his options to leave. A move to former club Sheffield United failed to materialise as their takeover faltered, but the most serious interest emerged from Bayern Munich. Thomas Tuchel has pushed hard to land Walker and they offered the England defender a substantial offer to make the move, but 90min understands that Guardiola has persuaded the 33-year-old to extend his stay with the club. Walker's current deal is due to expire at the end of the 2023\/24 season but this will be extended to 2025 with new terms. And the news continues to be positive at Man City as their similarly firm stance on Silva looks set to pay off. feed Silva has been looking to leave the club and there have been no shortage of suitors, with Barcelona pushing hard to sign a player who had long been eyeing a move to Catalonia. PSG were ready to pay Man City their asking price of around  £80m this summer, but Silva has been told he will not be allowed to leave. While Silva is keen to move on from Man City and has recently reiterated that desire to Guardiola, sources have told 90min that he is accepting there is little chance of any club being able to persuade them to sell. Silva's current deal runs to 2025, which means Man City are not under pressure to sanction a transfer, and because of that a new contract is now close to being finalised. As 90min previously revealed, Man City are willing to make Silva one of the best-paid players at the club and in the Premier League altogether, putting him close to the wage packets of teammates Erling Haaland and Kevin De Bruyne. Man City believe and hope that both Silva and Walker will put pen-to-paper on their new deals by the end of this month.","label":[[0,15,"ORG"],[49,63,"PER"],[68,79,"PER"],[150,155,"ORG"],[319,331,"PER"],[340,354,"PER"],[374,382,"ORG"],[388,401,"PER"],[465,470,"PER"],[475,481,"PER"],[508,513,"ORG"],[548,554,"PER"],[561,567,"PER"],[604,624,"ORG"],[699,715,"ORG"],[809,822,"ORG"],[824,837,"PER"],[862,868,"PER"],[949,954,"ORG"],[972,981,"PER"],[1046,1054,"PER"],[1103,1110,"DAT"],[1147,1151,"DAT"],[1209,1217,"ORG"],[1252,1257,"PER"],[1285,1290,"PER"],[1375,1384,"ORG"],[1450,1459,"LOC"],[1461,1464,"ORG"],[1483,1491,"ORG"],[1522,1526,"MON"],[1544,1549,"PER"],[1603,1608,"PER"],[1633,1641,"ORG"],[1685,1694,"PER"],[1714,1719,"ORG"],[1813,1820,"PER"],[1842,1846,"DAT"],[1860,1868,"ORG"],[1987,1992,"ORG"],[2014,2022,"ORG"],[2043,2048,"PER"],[2097,2115,"ORG"],[2179,2193,"PER"],[2198,2213,"PER"],[2215,2223,"ORG"],[2251,2256,"PER"],[2261,2267,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":80,"text":"Manchester United are set to enter the transfer market to sign a new centre-back following the completion of Harry Maguire's  £30m move to West Ham, 90min understands. Maguire is in discussions over a move to east London after being made available for transfer this summer by Erik ten Hag, who has already stripped the 30-year-old of the United captaincy. Maguire had initially wanted to stay and fight for his place but is now likely to proceed with his Old Trafford departure after talks between the clubs progressed this week. The England international arrived in 2019 for  £80m, a world record transfer fee for a defender, but has suffered a difficult four years under successive managers Ten Hag, Ralf Rangnick and Ole Gunnar Solskjaer. He has lost his place entirely in the team under the Dutchman, who has not deemed Maguire suitable to execute the style of football he'd like to implement in Manchester. It had been part of Ten Hag's long-term plan to phase out and replace Maguire, despite his public suggestions otherwise, and now his departure is nearing completion, United are exploring names to replace his position in the squad. They have been offered Benjamin Pavard, a French World Cup winner who has been looking to leave Bayern Munich for the duration of the summer. He would carry the added bonus of being able to cover at right-back should he swap southern Germany for north west England. Bayern are open to letting Pavard leave and he'd likely cost United in the region of what they'd receive for Maguire. feed Nice centre-back Jean-Clair Todibo is a younger alternative at a similar price under consideration, while Liverpool target Perr Schuurs, now of Torino but formerly of Ten Hag's Ajax, is also liked behind the scenes. Everton's Jarrad Branthwaite is another central defender United have been following. Edmond Tapsoba, a Tottenham target who plays for Bayer Leverkusen, represents a more expensive option if United choose to go down that route, though it remains to be seen at present how much they are prepared to outlay and how ambitious they'd like to be with their replacement. Benfica's Antonio Silva is understood to be loved by club scouts but potentially the most expensive of those named. The club are looking to raise funds through the sales of a number of squad players - not just that of Maguire - and are close to moving Fred out of Old Trafford, with several parties interested in the Brazilian. Donny van de Beek is also set to depart for Real Sociedad in the coming weeks, with United pushing for a permanent deal, while Scott McTominay is still of interest to West Ham, who are now threatened by interest from Manchester City in Lucas Paqueta.","label":[[0,17,"ORG"],[109,124,"PER"],[126,130,"MON"],[139,147,"ORG"],[149,154,"ORG"],[168,175,"PER"],[209,220,"LOC"],[276,288,"PER"],[356,363,"PER"],[455,467,"LOC"],[534,541,"ORG"],[567,571,"DAT"],[577,581,"MON"],[693,700,"PER"],[702,715,"PER"],[720,740,"PER"],[824,831,"PER"],[900,910,"ORG"],[932,941,"PER"],[982,989,"PER"],[1078,1084,"ORG"],[1166,1181,"PER"],[1192,1201,"ORG"],[1239,1252,"ORG"],[1368,1384,"LOC"],[1389,1407,"LOC"],[1409,1415,"ORG"],[1436,1442,"PER"],[1470,1476,"ORG"],[1518,1525,"PER"],[1532,1536,"ORG"],[1549,1566,"PER"],[1638,1647,"ORG"],[1655,1667,"PER"],[1676,1682,"LOC"],[1699,1708,"PER"],[1709,1713,"ORG"],[1748,1757,"ORG"],[1758,1776,"PER"],[1805,1811,"ORG"],[1833,1847,"PER"],[1851,1860,"ORG"],[1882,1898,"ORG"],[1938,1944,"ORG"],[2112,2121,"ORG"],[2122,2135,"PER"],[2330,2337,"PER"],[2364,2368,"PER"],[2376,2388,"LOC"],[2440,2457,"PER"],[2484,2497,"ORG"],[2524,2530,"ORG"],[2567,2582,"PER"],[2607,2615,"ORG"],[2657,2672,"ORG"],[2676,2689,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":81,"text":"Chelsea's pursuit of Leeds United midfielder Tyler Adams has broken down, 90min understands, with the United States international now heading back to his current club. The Blues triggered the  £20m relegation release clause in Adams' Leeds contract and the 24-year-old travelled down to London to finalise the terms of a move to Stamford Bridge, but negotiations have now collapsed. Sources have confirmed to 90min that Adams is now heading back to Leeds, with Chelsea no longer pursuing an agreement. The collapse in talks in the latest event in a hectic 24 hours for Chelsea, who find themselves embroiled in battles with Liverpool over both Brighton's Moises Caicedo and Southampton's Romeo Lavia. feed Chelsea's current focus remains Caicedo, with the Blues refusing to give up on the Ecuador international even after Liverpool saw a British record  £111m bid accepted by Brighton. While Chelsea have not yet improved their bid of  £80m, they continue to explore their options in the hope of convincing Caicedo to choose Stamford Bridge over Anfield. At the same time, Lavia remains a real option for both Chelsea and Liverpool. The former have the highest bid as it stands, offering  £48m for the 19-year-old despite Southampton's asking price of  £50m.","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[21,33,"ORG"],[45,56,"PER"],[74,79,"ORG"],[102,115,"ORG"],[168,177,"ORG"],[193,197,"MON"],[227,232,"PER"],[234,239,"ORG"],[287,293,"LOC"],[329,344,"LOC"],[409,414,"ORG"],[420,425,"PER"],[449,454,"ORG"],[461,468,"ORG"],[569,576,"ORG"],[624,633,"ORG"],[644,654,"ORG"],[655,669,"PER"],[674,687,"ORG"],[688,699,"PER"],[706,715,"ORG"],[738,745,"PER"],[752,761,"ORG"],[789,796,"ORG"],[822,831,"ORG"],[854,859,"MON"],[876,884,"ORG"],[892,899,"ORG"],[936,940,"MON"],[1007,1014,"PER"],[1025,1040,"LOC"],[1046,1053,"LOC"],[1073,1078,"PER"],[1110,1117,"ORG"],[1122,1131,"ORG"],[1189,1193,"MON"],[1222,1235,"ORG"],[1253,1257,"MON"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":82,"text":"Jurgen Klopp is never shy in expressing his vehement distaste for numerous aspects of modern football's calendar. Whether it's Saturday lunchtime kick-offs or England's festive fixture list, the Liverpool manager is quick to voice his criticism. The latest scheduling conflict to irk Klopp has been the closing date of the Saudi Pro League's summer transfer window. \"I think pretty much the worst thing is that the transfer window in Saudi Arabia is three weeks longer open,\" Klopp argued ahead of the new Premier League season. \"That's not helpful. So there must be, UEFA, FIFA must find solutions for that.\" Klopp knows the power that the Pro League wields better than most after watching two of his starting midfielders Jordan Henderson and Fabinho move to the Middle East this summer. Here's exactly when the Saudi Pro League transfer window closes and how it compares to its European counterparts. Much like most European divisions and northern hemisphere leagues in general, the Saudi Pro League transfer window began on 1 July. Before the window had even officially opened, Saudi clubs had begun to reshape the transfer market with the earth-shattering arrival of Karim Benzema at top-flight champions Al Ittihad. While Cristiano Ronaldo's move to Al Nassr last December was ground-breaking, the acquisition of the reigning Ballon d'Or winner was a statement move. There is still plenty of time for many more. The Saudi Arabian sports ministry has put aside around $800m ( £628m) for transfers to the top flight this summer, per the New York Times. The newly expanded 18-team league has until 20 September to splurge this hulking mass of capital. According to the detailed report in the New York Times, Saudi clubs were each provided with numerous transfer recommendations at the start of the window alongside a set of ground rules to prevent inter-league competition for players. During the seismic off-season, Saudi clubs have spent around  £350m to recruit the likes of Benzema, former Manchester City winger Riyad Mahrez and Sadio Mane from Bayern Munich. No team among Europe's supposed elite has proven capable of matching the financial might from the Middle East. The Saudi Pro League's chief operating officer Carlo Nohra explained to Reuters: \"We had to improve quality and in order to improve quality, you have to bring in the best. Spending was always going to be an essential component for us to do this.\" manual Klopp's outburst was underpinned by the disparity between the closing dates of the transfer windows in England and Saudi Arabia. While the Pro League can continue to tempt players away with lucrative deals until the fourth week of September, the Premier League's transfer window slams (it never closes quietly) shut on 1 September at 23:00 BST. When both windows are open, Premier League clubs can at least source replacements for the individuals that chased gold to the Gulf. Yet, there are 19 long days for Saudi sides to pilfer England's helpless top flight. According to FIFA's Regulations on the Status and Transfer of Players, transfer windows are determined by each association. World football's governing body stipulates that there must be two registration periods (summer and winter windows) and the first \"shall begin on the first day of the season. This period may not exceed 12 weeks.\" The 2023\/24 season begins on 1 July 2023 for most leagues which run from autumn to spring. Therefore, the latest that the summer window could close would be on 23 September 2023. The Saudi Pro League have simply stretched the window to its limits while the Premier League plays by the same rules as the rest of Europe. League Closing date \/ time (BST) La Liga 01\/09\/2023 - 23:00 Serie A 01\/09\/2023 - 19:00 Bundesliga 01\/09\/2023 - 17:00 Ligue 1 01\/09\/2023 - 22:00 This year, all of the major European leagues will also close at varying times on 1 September. The Premier League voted to close their summer window in 2018 and 2019 when the season's fixtures began during August, theoretically providing every manager with a settled squad for each match in the first half of the campaign. However, the rest of Europe didn't follow suit, giving those on the continent ample opportunity to poach Premier League stars without any chance of retaliation. After two years, Premier League clubs voted to get back \"in sync\" with the rest of Europe. Now, the continent's elite teams are out of step with the Saudi Pro League - which has already spent more on transfers than La Liga. Whether this will lead to an extension of future summer windows remains to be seen. But there will be no solution for a grumpy Klopp this year.","label":[[0,12,"PER"],[195,204,"ORG"],[284,289,"PER"],[319,341,"ORG"],[434,446,"LOC"],[476,481,"PER"],[506,520,"ORG"],[568,572,"ORG"],[574,578,"ORG"],[610,615,"PER"],[641,652,"ORG"],[723,739,"PER"],[744,751,"PER"],[764,775,"LOC"],[813,829,"ORG"],[985,1001,"ORG"],[1027,1033,"DAT"],[1171,1184,"PER"],[1209,1219,"ORG"],[1227,1246,"PER"],[1255,1263,"ORG"],[1269,1277,"DAT"],[1472,1477,"MON"],[1480,1485,"MON"],[1536,1554,"ORG"],[1600,1612,"DAT"],[1690,1708,"ORG"],[1950,1955,"MON"],[1980,1987,"PER"],[1996,2011,"ORG"],[2019,2031,"PER"],[2036,2046,"PER"],[2052,2065,"ORG"],[2161,2176,"LOC"],[2178,2200,"ORG"],[2225,2236,"PER"],[2250,2257,"ORG"],[2432,2439,"PER"],[2535,2542,"LOC"],[2547,2559,"LOC"],[2571,2581,"ORG"],[2678,2694,"ORG"],[2751,2762,"DAT"],[2766,2775,"TIM"],[2805,2819,"ORG"],[2941,2946,"LOC"],[3007,3013,"ORG"],[3334,3341,"DAT"],[3359,3370,"DAT"],[3490,3507,"DAT"],[3513,3529,"ORG"],[3587,3601,"ORG"],[3641,3647,"LOC"],[3682,3689,"ORG"],[3690,3700,"DAT"],[3703,3708,"TIM"],[3709,3716,"ORG"],[3717,3727,"DAT"],[3730,3735,"TIM"],[3736,3746,"ORG"],[3747,3757,"DAT"],[3760,3765,"TIM"],[3766,3773,"ORG"],[3774,3784,"DAT"],[3787,3792,"TIM"],[3874,3885,"DAT"],[3891,3905,"ORG"],[3944,3948,"DAT"],[3953,3957,"DAT"],[3998,4004,"DAT"],[4136,4142,"LOC"],[4220,4234,"ORG"],[4293,4307,"ORG"],[4359,4365,"LOC"],[4425,4441,"ORG"],[4491,4498,"ORG"],[4627,4632,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":83,"text":"Tottenham Hotspur head coach Ange Postecoglou has admitted that Harry Kane was 'unlikely' to stay at the club this season ahead of his move to Bayern Munich. 90min reported on Thursday that Spurs had finally relented and accepted an  £86.4m (   100m) bid from the German champions. Kane will fly to Germany on Friday to finalise the transfer. Spurs boss Postecoglou insisted last week that he simply wanted the saga resolved as soon as possible to plan for the season ahead. Ahead of Sunday's trip to Brentford for his Premier League debut, Postecoglou was understandably asked for an update on Kane. \"It's fair to say I don't have a blow by blow account of the whole thing but fair to say it's progressed to the point where it looks like it's going to happen. We move forward without Harry. It gives us clarity and unless something unforeseen happens we'll move on,\" he said. \"I didn't see the point in [pitching myself] because whatever I was going to say was going to be irrelevant. I could plan his grand vision but I'm sure he'd heard it all before. My feeling was we'll get to know each other, that's the best way to navigate this early bit. Having said that, in my mind after that initial conversation [on the first day], he'd made up his mind that if the clubs agreed he'd go but he was also happy to stay if they didn't. \"It's best Harry speaks for himself on the decision but there's no doubts he's one of the greats of this football club. His record speaks for himself. I'm only new in the building but I'm certainly not the spokesman for this football club in declaring people's status but I think it's clear Harry Kane is one of the greats. \"I think if you're involved in football as long as I have, you know clubs are not going to talk to each other without the player knowing. We weren't talking to Wolfsburg without knowing Micky van de Ven wanted to come. \"[Harry and I] had a chat on the first day. He was up front and honest that if they could agree a deal then he would go. He wanted it decided by the first game and that was my preference as well.\" manual When asked how Tottenham will go about replacing Kane, Postecoglou added: \"I don't think there's a like for like replacement for Harry. We've been planning for this for a while to be fair. It doesn't take too much investigative work to know that this was going to happen. Our business up to now reflects that. \"I don't think it works that way [giving Daniel Levy a list of strikers to get]. It's not like the family shopping list to go and get milk and bread for the kids. My whole strategy has been that Harry was unlikely to be around so it wasn't like we had a pow wow this morning.\" 90min revealed earlier this week that Spurs representatives had touched base with other forwards, including Gent starlet Gift Orban.","label":[[0,17,"ORG"],[29,45,"PER"],[64,74,"PER"],[143,156,"ORG"],[158,163,"ORG"],[190,195,"ORG"],[234,240,"MON"],[245,249,"MON"],[282,286,"PER"],[299,306,"LOC"],[343,348,"ORG"],[354,365,"PER"],[501,510,"ORG"],[519,533,"ORG"],[541,552,"PER"],[595,599,"PER"],[785,790,"PER"],[1341,1346,"PER"],[1621,1631,"PER"],[1814,1823,"ORG"],[1840,1856,"PER"],[1875,1880,"PER"],[2092,2101,"ORG"],[2126,2130,"PER"],[2132,2143,"PER"],[2206,2211,"PER"],[2428,2439,"PER"],[2582,2587,"PER"],[2664,2669,"ORG"],[2702,2707,"ORG"],[2772,2776,"ORG"],[2785,2795,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":84,"text":"West Ham United manager David Moyes has provided an update on the club's pursuit of Manchester United defender Harry Maguire. 90min reported on Wednesday that the two clubs had agreed terms on a  £30m transfer fee after the Hammers agreed to up their wage offer. Ahead of West Ham's Premier League season opener away to Bournemouth, Moyes was asked for the latest on the saga. \"We've had a bid accepted from Manchester United, but while he's not our player I'm not in a position to discuss him,\" he replied. feed While Maguire has not officially left the club yet, 90min understands Man Utd are stepping up plans to bring in a replacement centre-back. Bayern Munich's Benjamin Pavard has been offered to the Red Devils and has made it clear in recent months that he wants to continue his playing career at centre-back as opposed to right-back. Nice's Jean-Clair Todibo, Everton's Jarrad Branthwaite, Torino's Perr Schuurs and Bayer Leverkusen's Edmond Tapsoba are all on Man Utd's shortlist. Maguire was stripped of the club captaincy this summer and removed entirely from Man Utd's leadership group, with Bruno Fernandes being promoted to skipper. West Ham, meanwhile, have finally made some movement in the transfer market after a quiet summer window. They recently completed the signing of Ajax midfielder Edson Alvarez, with Southampton captain James Ward-Prowse set to follow.","label":[[0,15,"ORG"],[24,35,"PER"],[84,101,"ORG"],[111,124,"PER"],[126,131,"ORG"],[196,200,"MON"],[220,231,"ORG"],[272,282,"ORG"],[283,297,"ORG"],[320,331,"ORG"],[333,338,"PER"],[408,425,"ORG"],[519,526,"PER"],[565,570,"ORG"],[583,590,"ORG"],[652,667,"ORG"],[668,683,"PER"],[704,718,"ORG"],[844,850,"ORG"],[851,868,"PER"],[870,879,"ORG"],[880,898,"PER"],[900,908,"ORG"],[909,921,"PER"],[926,944,"ORG"],[945,959,"PER"],[971,980,"ORG"],[992,999,"PER"],[1073,1082,"ORG"],[1106,1121,"PER"],[1149,1157,"ORG"],[1293,1297,"ORG"],[1309,1322,"PER"],[1329,1340,"ORG"],[1349,1366,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":85,"text":"Liverpool manager Jurgen Klopp admits his previous comments on heavy spending were wrong  in the wake of the Reds'  £111m agreement to sign Moises Caicedo from Brighton. Caicedo is set to become the most expensive signing in the history of English football after Liverpool agreed to pay Brighton  £111m to sign the midfielder, but critics were quick to recall Klopp's previous criticisms of such heavy spending. Indeed, in 2016, Klopp was left stunned by Manchester United's  £89m acquisition of Paul Pogba - a world record at the time - and vowed he would never pull the trigger on such a deal. \"The day that this is football, I'm not in a job anymore, because the game is about playing together,\" Klopp said at the time. \"Other clubs can go out and spend more money and collect top players. I want to do it differently. I would even do it differently if I could spend that money.\" feed Having now agreed to sign Caicedo for  £111m in the same summer as Dominik Szoboszlai and Alexis Mac Allister moved to Liverpool for a combined  £95m, Klopp confessed the market has been thrown into turmoil since his comments on Pogba. \"Everything changed,\" he told a press conference on Friday. \"Do I like it? No, but did I realise I was wrong? Definitely. Definitely. That's the way it goes. It's not great, it's not top. Saudi Arabia will not help with that. I'm not blaming it, but another market with a lot of money. \"In the end, we as a club, we have to try make sure that we, with our resources, get the best possible team together. We try everything to bring together the best squad for us, and we are not in dreamland, so it's not like we can just point at players and bring them in. \"If people want to throw my quotes from five or six years ago at me, no problem. That's what I thought that day, and I realise now I was wrong, easy to admit that.\"","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[18,30,"PER"],[105,113,"PER"],[116,121,"MON"],[140,154,"PER"],[160,168,"ORG"],[170,177,"PER"],[263,272,"ORG"],[287,295,"ORG"],[297,302,"MON"],[360,367,"PER"],[423,427,"DAT"],[429,434,"PER"],[455,474,"ORG"],[476,480,"MON"],[496,506,"PER"],[699,704,"PER"],[914,921,"PER"],[927,932,"MON"],[955,973,"PER"],[978,997,"PER"],[1007,1016,"ORG"],[1033,1037,"MON"],[1039,1044,"PER"],[1117,1122,"PER"],[1312,1324,"LOC"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":86,"text":"90min  rounds up the latest  transfer news, rumours and gossip circulating around the world... Neymar is willing to sanction a move to the Saudi Pro League this summer, but only on the condition he is allowed to spend the 2023\/24 season on loan at Barcelona. (SPORT) PSG believe Kylian Mbappe will earn    160m ( £137.6m) from a sign-on fee if he joins Real Madrid on a free transfer next summer and so have set his price tag this window at a similar figure. (CaughtOffside) Harry Maguire has indicated he is happy to join West Ham if they agree a fee with Manchester United. The Hammers have seen a  £30m bid for the defender knocked back by the Red Devils, with Scott McTominay also a target. (Evening Standard) In the event that Maguire leaves, Manchester United will step up interest in Nice centre-back Jean-Clair Todibo, who was once on the books at Barcelona. (RMC Sport) David Raya will undergo a medical at Arsenal after the Gunners agreed a  £30m fee with Brentford. (Fabrizio Romano) Brighton CEO Paul Barber has admitted interest from Chelsea has unsettled Moises Caicedo amid reports the midfielder is skipping training to force through a move to Stamford Bridge. (Sky Sports) manual While Chelsea also have an interest in Romeo Lavia, Liverpool are not worried that their proposed move for the Belgium international will be hijacked. The 19-year-old was left out of the Southampton squad which lost to Gillingham in the Carabao Cup on Tuesday night. (Daily Express) Tottenham are 'resigned' to losing Harry Kane after Bayern Munich signalled they are willing to up their bid to  £94.6m (   110m). Spurs would use this money to bring in a new striker as well as stock up in midfield and at centre-back. (The Times) In their search for a new goalkeeper, Bayern Munich have added Chelsea's Kepa Arrizabalaga to their shortlist. The Spaniard has previously worked under Thomas Tuchel. (SPORT1) Manchester City are set to have a  £70m bid for Lucas Paqueta rejected by West Ham, with the treble-winners now keen to add the Brazil international to their ranks. (Ge Globo)","label":[[0,5,"ORG"],[95,101,"PER"],[139,155,"ORG"],[222,229,"DAT"],[248,257,"ORG"],[260,265,"ORG"],[267,270,"ORG"],[279,292,"PER"],[306,310,"MON"],[313,320,"MON"],[353,364,"ORG"],[460,473,"ORG"],[475,488,"PER"],[523,531,"PER"],[557,574,"ORG"],[576,587,"ORG"],[601,605,"MON"],[643,657,"ORG"],[664,679,"PER"],[696,712,"ORG"],[732,739,"PER"],[748,765,"ORG"],[791,795,"ORG"],[808,825,"PER"],[856,865,"ORG"],[868,877,"ORG"],[879,889,"PER"],[916,923,"ORG"],[930,941,"ORG"],[952,956,"MON"],[966,975,"ORG"],[978,993,"PER"],[995,1003,"ORG"],[1008,1019,"PER"],[1047,1054,"ORG"],[1069,1083,"PER"],[1160,1175,"LOC"],[1178,1188,"ORG"],[1203,1210,"ORG"],[1236,1247,"PER"],[1249,1258,"ORG"],[1308,1315,"ORG"],[1384,1395,"ORG"],[1416,1426,"ORG"],[1430,1445,"ORG"],[1465,1478,"ORG"],[1480,1489,"ORG"],[1515,1525,"PER"],[1532,1545,"ORG"],[1593,1599,"MON"],[1604,1608,"MON"],[1611,1616,"ORG"],[1717,1726,"ORG"],[1766,1779,"ORG"],[1791,1800,"ORG"],[1801,1818,"PER"],[1880,1893,"PER"],[1896,1902,"ORG"],[1904,1919,"ORG"],[1939,1943,"MON"],[1952,1965,"PER"],[1978,1986,"ORG"],[2032,2038,"ORG"],[2070,2079,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":87,"text":"West Ham United have agreed a  £30m deal with Southampton for their captain James Ward-Prowse, sources have confirmed to 90min. The Hammers have been desperately trying to strengthen their squad after selling Declan Rice to Arsenal in a British-record  £105m transfer. Things have been slow moving for West Ham, amid internal conflicts between manager David Moyes and new technical director Tim Steidten, but progress has been made over the past 48 hours on a number of targets. Edson Alvarez has completed a medical in London ahead of a  £34m move from Ajax, while West Ham have also agreed a  £30m fee for former Manchester United skipper Harry Maguire - he is now due to discuss personal terms over a move to the East End. And sources have confirmed to 90min that after lengthy negotiations, West Ham have agreed a  £30m deal with Southampton for Ward-Prowse, with an additional sell-on clause, having seen a bid for the same amount rejected by United for Scott McTominay. feed It had looked as though West Ham's move for central midfielder Ward-Prowse would fall through, with Southampton wanting more money for the 28-year-old, but terms have now been agreed between the two parties ahead of the opening weekend of the Premier League season. It's expected he will sign a four-year contract should he come through a medical unscathed. Ward-Prowse has been at Southampton for the entirety of his career, making 422 appearances on the south coast and scoring 55 goals. He has also provided 55 assists in that time, while his unerring accuracy from free-kicks has drawn comparisons to David Beckham. West Ham hope to complete deals for half a dozen players before the summer window closes, with attention now set to turn to strengthening in the wide forward areas and with a striker.","label":[[0,15,"ORG"],[31,35,"MON"],[46,57,"ORG"],[76,93,"PER"],[121,126,"ORG"],[128,139,"ORG"],[209,220,"PER"],[224,231,"ORG"],[253,258,"MON"],[302,310,"ORG"],[352,363,"PER"],[391,403,"PER"],[479,492,"PER"],[520,526,"LOC"],[539,543,"MON"],[554,558,"ORG"],[566,574,"ORG"],[595,599,"MON"],[615,632,"ORG"],[641,654,"PER"],[712,724,"LOC"],[756,761,"ORG"],[795,803,"ORG"],[819,823,"MON"],[834,845,"ORG"],[850,861,"PER"],[948,954,"ORG"],[959,974,"PER"],[1005,1015,"ORG"],[1044,1055,"ORG"],[1081,1092,"ORG"],[1224,1238,"ORG"],[1339,1350,"PER"],[1363,1374,"ORG"],[1586,1599,"PER"],[1601,1609,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":88,"text":"Chelsea are refusing to give up their pursuit of Brighton midfielder Moises Caicedo, 90min understands, despite seeing Liverpool agree a fee for the Ecuador international. The Blues failed with an  £80m offer and were considering returning with a bid closer to Brighton's  £100m asking price when Liverpool swooped in and agreed a British record deal worth  £111m to sign the 21-year-old. Nothing has been signed between Brighton and Liverpool, however, and sources have confirmed to 90min that Chelsea are refusing to accept defeat in the race. Chelsea have informed Caicedo's representatives that they are prepared to battle to try and sign the midfielder and will not give up hope until he has put pen to paper on a deal with Liverpool. As it stands, Chelsea have not made a new bid for Caicedo, with Liverpool the only side to have seen an offer accepted. Before Liverpool's offer arrived, 90min understood that Caicedo's preference was to join Chelsea this summer, with the midfielder repeatedly making it clear to Brighton that he wanted to be allowed to speak to the Blues. feed Caicedo has not yet travelled to Merseyside for a scheduled medical, 90min further understands, and Chelsea are using the time to try and work on a solution. Brighton are hoping to sell Caicedo to the highest bidder and wasted little time in accepting Liverpool's offer, which was significantly higher than any proposal put forward until now by Chelsea. The two clubs, who ironically meet in their opening Premier League fixture on Sunday, have also butted heads  over Southampton midfielder Romeo Lavia. The Reds failed with three bids for the Belgian, the last of which was worth  £46m, before Chelsea arrived with an offer of  £48m. Southampton value Lavia at  £50m and are not prepared to compromise on their price. Where Caicedo ends up remains to be seen, but the twists and turns of the transfer have made it one of the most fascinating sagas of what's been an extraordinary window to date.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[49,57,"ORG"],[69,83,"PER"],[85,90,"ORG"],[119,128,"ORG"],[149,156,"ORG"],[172,181,"ORG"],[198,202,"MON"],[261,271,"ORG"],[273,278,"MON"],[297,306,"ORG"],[358,363,"MON"],[421,429,"ORG"],[434,443,"ORG"],[484,489,"ORG"],[495,502,"ORG"],[546,553,"ORG"],[568,577,"PER"],[729,738,"ORG"],[754,761,"ORG"],[790,797,"PER"],[804,813,"ORG"],[867,878,"ORG"],[894,899,"ORG"],[916,925,"PER"],[949,956,"ORG"],[1020,1028,"ORG"],[1070,1079,"ORG"],[1086,1093,"PER"],[1119,1129,"LOC"],[1155,1160,"ORG"],[1186,1193,"ORG"],[1244,1252,"ORG"],[1272,1279,"PER"],[1338,1349,"ORG"],[1431,1438,"ORG"],[1492,1506,"ORG"],[1555,1566,"ORG"],[1578,1589,"PER"],[1591,1599,"ORG"],[1669,1673,"MON"],[1682,1689,"ORG"],[1716,1720,"MON"],[1722,1733,"ORG"],[1740,1745,"PER"],[1750,1754,"MON"],[1812,1819,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
