{"id":1,"text":"Paris Saint-Germain have confirmed the signing of French winger Ousmane Dembele from Barcelona. Dembele had been in talks over extending his Barcelona contract before PSG voiced a desire to trigger the    50m release clause in the Frenchman's contract, and although that clause expired last month, Dembele's desire to seal the move saw Barcelona agree to the same terms. Having entered the final year of his contract at Camp Nou, Barcelona preferred to cash in on Dembele when it became clear he would leave for free next summer if he remained at the club. For Dembele, it's a return to Ligue 1 for the first time since he departed Rennes in 2016, with the 26-year-old inking a five-year contract at Parc des Princes. feed \"I'm delighted to be joining Paris Saint-Germain and can't wait to play for my new club,\" Dembele told club media. \"I hope I can continue to grow here and make all the club's fans proud.\" President Nasser Al-Khelaifi added: \"We are delighted to welcome Ousmane Dembele to Paris Saint-Germain where he will be an important and committed player for our club. \"The passion and determination shown by Ousmane as he has signed for PSG is fantastic and perfectly corresponds to the attitude required of all of our players. We are proud to be able to bring another French World Cup winner to Paris Saint-Germain as we enter a new great era for our club.    90min understands that PSG are also making progress in talks with Eintracht Frankfurt over striker Randal Kolo Muani, with the Bundesliga side now working on finding a replacement.","label":[[0,19,"ORG"],[64,79,"PER"],[85,94,"ORG"],[96,103,"PER"],[141,150,"ORG"],[167,170,"ORG"],[205,208,"MON"],[298,307,"PER"],[336,345,"ORG"],[420,428,"LOC"],[430,439,"ORG"],[464,471,"PER"],[561,568,"PER"],[587,594,"ORG"],[632,638,"ORG"],[642,646,"DAT"],[700,716,"LOC"],[752,771,"ORG"],[813,820,"PER"],[921,939,"PER"],[976,991,"PER"],[995,1014,"ORG"],[1120,1127,"PER"],[1149,1152,"ORG"],[1288,1297,"ORG"],[1308,1327,"ORG"],[1373,1378,"ORG"],[1396,1399,"ORG"],[1439,1458,"ORG"],[1472,1489,"PER"],[1500,1510,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":2,"text":"Chelsea are close to finalising an agreement with Southampton for the transfer of Romeo Lavia, sources have confirmed to 90min. The Blues have a long-standing interest in the midfielder having tried to sign him last summer just weeks after he first joined the Saints from Manchester City. They continued to monitor Lavia throughout his debut Premier League season, with the teenager breaking into the Belgium senior side despite Southampton's relegation. Liverpool have seen three bids for Lavia rejected by Southampton this summer as they did not meet their  £50m valuation, and the Merseysiders could now be beaten to his signature by Chelsea. feed 90min understands that a deal to take Lavia from St Mary's to Stamford Bridge worth  £55m is close to being agreed, roughly 24 hours after Chelsea reignited their interest in the 19-year-old. Lavia has not made a competitive appearance for Southampton this season due to intense speculation regarding a move away. Chelsea and Liverpool's transfer business in recent days has been intertwined. The Reds appeared to have beaten the Blues to Brighton's Moises Caicedo after launching a British-record  £111m bid on Friday morning, but the Ecuadorian is holding out for a move to west London instead. Though they intend to match Liverpool's mammoth offer in the coming hours, Brighton are yet to receive a new bid from Chelsea. Elsewhere, Chelsea have dropped their interest in Leeds United's Tyler Adams despite agreeing to pay his  £20m relegation release clause this week, with the USMNT captain now returning to Yorkshire.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[50,61,"ORG"],[82,93,"PER"],[121,126,"ORG"],[128,137,"ORG"],[272,287,"ORG"],[315,320,"PER"],[342,356,"ORG"],[401,408,"ORG"],[429,442,"ORG"],[455,464,"ORG"],[490,495,"PER"],[508,519,"ORG"],[560,564,"MON"],[584,596,"ORG"],[637,644,"ORG"],[651,656,"ORG"],[689,694,"PER"],[700,709,"LOC"],[713,728,"LOC"],[736,740,"MON"],[790,797,"ORG"],[843,848,"PER"],[891,902,"ORG"],[965,972,"ORG"],[977,988,"ORG"],[1044,1052,"ORG"],[1081,1086,"ORG"],[1090,1100,"ORG"],[1101,1115,"PER"],[1150,1155,"MON"],[1227,1238,"LOC"],[1276,1287,"ORG"],[1323,1331,"ORG"],[1366,1373,"ORG"],[1386,1393,"ORG"],[1425,1439,"ORG"],[1440,1451,"PER"],[1481,1485,"MON"],[1532,1537,"ORG"],[1563,1572,"LOC"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":3,"text":"Manchester United are in talks with Bayern Munich over the possible transfer of 2018 World Cup-winning defender Benjamin Pavard, 90min understands. The versatile Pavard, capable of playing as a centre-back or right-back, joined Bayern in 2019 and has entered the final year of his contract at the Allianz Arena. With Maguire in the process of leaving Old Trafford before next month   s transfer deadline, Pavard had been among a number of options to replace the former captain. As 90min revealed last week, United are preparing to enter the transfer market once Maguire   s exit is completed. The England international had initially wanted to stay and fight for his place, despite slipping down the pecking order last season and losing the captaincy early in pre-season. feed But the Red Devils agreed a  £30m fee with fellow Premier League side West Ham United. Talks have continued to hammer out the details of the proposed deal, although things have progressed slower than had been hoped. That being said, all parties expect a conclusion to still be reached soon. Pavard has been offered to United, with Nice   s Jean-Clair Todibo, ex-Ajax defender Perr Schuurs, Jarrad Branthwaite of Everton, one-time Tottenham target Edmond Tapsoba and Benfica   s Antonio Silva all considered by the club to replace Maguire. But it is the Pavard path on which United are now progressing and 90min understands that negotiations with Bayern over the transfer fee are taking place. The perennial German champions value the Frenchman at  £30m (   35m), which is higher than the  £25.9m (   30m) that United have so far proposed. That figure hasn   t yet convinced Bayern to sell, but the difference in valuation has not dissuaded the sides from continuing to talk.","label":[[0,17,"ORG"],[36,49,"ORG"],[80,84,"DAT"],[85,94,"ORG"],[112,127,"PER"],[129,134,"ORG"],[162,168,"PER"],[228,234,"ORG"],[238,242,"DAT"],[297,310,"LOC"],[317,324,"PER"],[351,363,"LOC"],[405,411,"PER"],[481,486,"ORG"],[507,513,"ORG"],[562,569,"PER"],[597,604,"ORG"],[784,794,"ORG"],[805,809,"MON"],[826,840,"ORG"],[846,861,"ORG"],[1067,1073,"PER"],[1094,1100,"ORG"],[1107,1111,"ORG"],[1116,1133,"PER"],[1138,1142,"ORG"],[1152,1164,"PER"],[1166,1184,"PER"],[1188,1195,"ORG"],[1206,1215,"ORG"],[1223,1237,"PER"],[1242,1249,"ORG"],[1254,1267,"PER"],[1306,1313,"PER"],[1329,1335,"PER"],[1350,1356,"ORG"],[1381,1386,"ORG"],[1422,1428,"ORG"],[1524,1528,"MON"],[1533,1536,"MON"],[1565,1571,"MON"],[1576,1579,"MON"],[1586,1592,"ORG"],[1650,1656,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":4,"text":"Moises Caicedo is no stranger to a drawn-out transfer saga. Years before Chelsea began peppering Brighton with dizzying offers only to be outbid by Liverpool, before the Blues bid  £115m to secure his services this week, Caicedo was the subject of a multi-club tussle while he was still in Ecuador with Independiente del Valle. Manchester United, AC Milan, Brighton, Chelsea and Belgian side Club Brugge were all interested in the midfielder after a rapid ascension in senior South American football. Three separate agencies also tried to represent Caicedo and get a slice of any potentially lucrative deal. Ultimately, Brighton cut through the chaos to snag Caicedo for just  £4.5m in 2021. After less than 50 starts for the Seagulls, the 21-year-old has now become one of the most expensive players in the history of the sport. Here's how Caicedo's  £115m move to Chelsea compares to the game's other costly sagas. Chelsea confirmed the signing of Caicedo after one of the most dramatic transfer sagas of recent times. The Blues had been pursuing the midfielder for the majority of the summer, however had been unwilling to make a bid over  £80m until Liverpool agreed to fork out  £111m for his services.  Despite an agreement between Liverpool and Brighton being struck, Caicedo was unwilling to agree to a move to Anfield, opening the door for Chelsea to swoop in and have a  £115m bid accepted for his services.  The midfielder has now put pen to paper on an eight-year deal at Stamford Bridge.  Caicedo has become the most expensive signing for Chelsea and any other British club. But where does he rank on a global scale? Ranking Player Signed Joined Fee 1 Neymar 2017 PSG  £198m 2 Kylian Mbappe 2018 PSG  £163m 3 Philippe Coutinho 2018 Barcelona  £142m 4 Ousmane Dembele 2017 Barcelona  £135m 5 Moises Caicedo 2023 Chelsea  £115m 6 Joao Felix 2019 Atletico Madrid  £113m 7 Enzo Fernandez 2023 Chelsea  £107m 8 Antoine Griezmann 2019 Barcelona  £107m 9 Declan Rice 2023 Arsenal  £105m 10 Jack Grealish 2021 Manchester City  £100m Less than four years after making his senior debut as a 17-year-old in the Ecuadorian top flight, Caicedo has become the fifth most expensive footballer of all time.  Even though Caicedo's fee has scratched nine digits, Neymar's move to PSG comfortably remains the most expensive in history, with the Ligue 1 giants paying  £198m for the forward's services.  Neymar's PSG teammate Kylian Mbappe is second on the list but could have moved into top spot after Al Hilal's  £259m offer was accepted by the French champions. Mbappe ultimately refused to even meet with representatives of the Saudi giants.","label":[[0,14,"PER"],[73,80,"ORG"],[97,105,"ORG"],[148,157,"ORG"],[170,175,"ORG"],[181,186,"MON"],[221,228,"PER"],[290,297,"LOC"],[303,326,"ORG"],[328,345,"ORG"],[347,355,"ORG"],[357,365,"ORG"],[367,374,"ORG"],[392,403,"ORG"],[549,556,"PER"],[620,628,"ORG"],[659,666,"PER"],[677,682,"MON"],[686,690,"DAT"],[722,734,"ORG"],[841,850,"PER"],[852,857,"MON"],[866,873,"ORG"],[917,924,"ORG"],[950,957,"PER"],[1021,1030,"ORG"],[1143,1147,"MON"],[1154,1163,"ORG"],[1184,1189,"MON"],[1238,1247,"ORG"],[1252,1260,"ORG"],[1275,1282,"PER"],[1319,1326,"LOC"],[1349,1356,"ORG"],[1381,1386,"MON"],[1484,1499,"LOC"],[1502,1509,"PER"],[1552,1559,"ORG"],[1665,1671,"PER"],[1672,1676,"DAT"],[1677,1680,"ORG"],[1682,1687,"MON"],[1690,1703,"PER"],[1704,1708,"DAT"],[1709,1712,"ORG"],[1714,1719,"MON"],[1722,1739,"PER"],[1740,1744,"DAT"],[1745,1754,"ORG"],[1756,1761,"MON"],[1764,1779,"PER"],[1780,1784,"DAT"],[1785,1794,"ORG"],[1796,1801,"MON"],[1804,1818,"PER"],[1819,1823,"DAT"],[1824,1831,"ORG"],[1833,1838,"MON"],[1841,1851,"PER"],[1852,1856,"DAT"],[1857,1872,"ORG"],[1874,1879,"MON"],[1882,1896,"PER"],[1897,1901,"DAT"],[1902,1909,"ORG"],[1911,1916,"MON"],[1919,1936,"PER"],[1937,1941,"DAT"],[1942,1951,"ORG"],[1953,1958,"MON"],[1961,1972,"PER"],[1973,1977,"DAT"],[1978,1985,"ORG"],[1987,1992,"MON"],[1996,2009,"PER"],[2010,2014,"DAT"],[2015,2030,"ORG"],[2032,2037,"MON"],[2136,2143,"PER"],[2217,2226,"PER"],[2258,2266,"PER"],[2275,2278,"ORG"],[2339,2346,"ORG"],[2362,2367,"MON"],[2397,2405,"PER"],[2406,2409,"ORG"],[2419,2432,"PER"],[2496,2506,"ORG"],[2508,2513,"MON"],[2558,2564,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":5,"text":"Saudi Pro League director of football Michael Emenalo claims the competition can position itself as one of the world's best within the next two years by targeting 'exceptional players only' The former technical director of Chelsea assumed his role in July and is continuing the Pro League's significant  £400m investment initiative. This strategy has enticed players such as Karim Benzema, Jordan Henderson, Riyad Mahrez, and Roberto Firmino to join Saudi Arabian clubs this summer. So far, the majority of top stars heading to Saudi Arabia, including Benzema, N'Golo Kante and Cristiano Ronaldo, have been in the latter stages of their respective careers. At 26, Ruben Neves is one of the exceptions to the trend and arguably not in the same bracket of star anyway. Richard Masters, chief executive of the Premier League, recently shared that he isn't overly worried about Saudi Arabia's unrestricted spending. However, Emenalo cautioned that there are essentially no bounds to the country's willingness to invest in football players.  \"I would love  to have Kylian Mbappe here. I would love to have Harry Kane here. The league would like all the top players,\" he said. Indeed, Mbappe has already been the subject of world record  £259m bid from Al Hilal that was accepted by Paris Saint-Germain, although the plater himself wasn't interested in the move. manual \"In a couple of years, this will become a league for exceptional players only. It will become a league for those who are at the top of their game. We have the resources, and we   re going to use them,\" Emenalo said. \"I don   t think it is going to take the same amount of time that it took the [English] Premier League to get there for us to establish ourselves.\" Emenalo emphasised that the Saudi Pro League's aim is not to undermine the Premier League in a manner similar to LIV Golf and the PGA Tour and hopes that elite football's established order in Europe will eventually be less apprehensive and collaborate with them.    The European leagues, especially the Premier League, are very strong, they have no reason to be scared,    he added.    I think there   s panic in some areas, but this is from a misunderstanding of what we are trying to do.    I saw what [Jurgen] Klopp and what [Pep] Guardiola said [about the Pro League]. One is a coach I absolutely admire and the other is a good friend of mine in Pep. First, I hope they don   t talk themselves out of a job [in Saudi Arabia] in the future. I understand their concerns. Our goal is to work together with all the leagues and be a brotherhood in the football industry.   ","label":[[0,16,"ORG"],[38,53,"PER"],[223,230,"ORG"],[251,255,"DAT"],[278,290,"ORG"],[304,309,"MON"],[375,388,"PER"],[390,406,"PER"],[408,420,"PER"],[426,441,"PER"],[528,539,"LOC"],[552,559,"PER"],[561,573,"PER"],[578,595,"PER"],[664,675,"PER"],[767,782,"PER"],[807,821,"ORG"],[874,888,"LOC"],[921,928,"PER"],[1060,1073,"PER"],[1101,1111,"PER"],[1179,1185,"PER"],[1232,1237,"MON"],[1247,1255,"ORG"],[1277,1296,"ORG"],[1566,1573,"PER"],[1668,1682,"ORG"],[1728,1735,"PER"],[1756,1774,"ORG"],[1803,1817,"ORG"],[1841,1849,"ORG"],[1858,1866,"ORG"],[1920,1926,"LOC"],[2031,2045,"ORG"],[2232,2246,"PER"],[2256,2271,"PER"],[2378,2381,"PER"],[2443,2455,"LOC"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":6,"text":"Harry Maguire's proposed transfer to West Ham United has collapsed, 90min understands. After telling Maguire he is free to leave Old Trafford this summer, Manchester United initially rejected a  £30m bid from West Ham amid concerns over their ability to satisfy the centre-back's wage demands, only to eventually agree to the offer on the table. West Ham have since completed the signings of Edson Alvarez and James Ward-Prowse but talks over Maguire continued to drag on as they sought to thrash out a wage agreement with both the defender and United. 90min understands that Maguire had agreed the terms of a reduced contract with West Ham but sought a pay-off from United to compensate him for the loss in salary over the remaining two years of his deal at Old Trafford. Sources have now confirmed that no agreement was reached between Maguire and United, forcing West Ham to accept defeat in their pursuit of the centre-back. feed United had been preparing for Maguire's exit by speaking with Bayern Munich over French defender Benjamin Pavard but, as 90min revealed earlier this summer, the Red Devils fear they do not have the financial room to sign another defender with Maguire's high wages still on the books. There has been tentative interest in Maguire from elsewhere but United are not expecting more bids for the 30-year-old, who appears set to remain at Old Trafford beyond this summer. Manager Erik ten Hag is known to be happy to continue working with Maguire as a backup to Raphael Varane and Lisandro Martinez, but he recently warned the England international that he is in for a fight for minutes if he chooses to stay. Maguire remains under contract at United until 2025, with the club holding the option to extend his deal by a further 12 months.","label":[[0,15,"PER"],[37,52,"ORG"],[68,73,"ORG"],[101,108,"PER"],[129,141,"LOC"],[155,172,"ORG"],[195,199,"MON"],[209,217,"ORG"],[346,354,"ORG"],[392,405,"PER"],[410,427,"PER"],[443,450,"PER"],[545,551,"ORG"],[553,558,"ORG"],[576,583,"PER"],[632,640,"ORG"],[667,673,"ORG"],[759,771,"LOC"],[838,845,"PER"],[850,856,"ORG"],[866,874,"ORG"],[934,940,"ORG"],[964,973,"PER"],[996,1009,"ORG"],[1031,1046,"PER"],[1055,1060,"ORG"],[1095,1105,"ORG"],[1177,1186,"PER"],[1255,1262,"PER"],[1282,1288,"ORG"],[1367,1379,"LOC"],[1408,1420,"PER"],[1467,1474,"PER"],[1490,1504,"PER"],[1509,1526,"PER"],[1555,1562,"ORG"],[1638,1645,"PER"],[1672,1678,"ORG"],[1685,1689,"DAT"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":7,"text":"Everton have finalised a deal to bring in Leeds United winger Jack Harrison on a season-long loan, sources have confirmed to 90min. The former Manchester City and New York City winger will join Everton for the 2023\/24 campaign after activating a clause in his contract following Leeds' relegation from the Premier League. Aston Villa also made a move for Harrison, but upon learning that he would not be fit for another six weeks, they backed away from a deal - Villa are looking at options in the transfer market having lost Emi Buendia to an ACL injury and they wanted someone who could make an immediate impact. Harrison passed a medical with Everton on Sunday but he does have a hip problem that will likely see him sidelined until after the September international break. feed Everton turned to Harrison after accepting defeat in their pursuit of his teammate Willy Gnonto. The Italy international agreed personal terms over a move to Goodison Park, but Leeds would not allow him to leave. Gnonto was one of the few Leeds players in their squad that did not have some sort of release clause, unlike Harrison. Harrison is the latest Leeds player to depart the West Yorkshire giants this summer after returning to the Championship. Rodrigo, Robin Koch, Max Wober, Tyler Roberts, Joel Robles, Brenden Aaronson, Rasmus Kristensen and Marc Roca have all departed the club.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[42,54,"ORG"],[62,75,"PER"],[125,130,"ORG"],[143,158,"ORG"],[163,176,"ORG"],[194,201,"ORG"],[210,217,"DAT"],[279,284,"ORG"],[306,320,"ORG"],[322,333,"ORG"],[355,363,"PER"],[462,467,"ORG"],[526,537,"PER"],[615,623,"PER"],[646,653,"ORG"],[746,755,"DAT"],[782,789,"ORG"],[800,808,"PER"],[865,877,"PER"],[883,888,"ORG"],[940,953,"LOC"],[959,964,"ORG"],[995,1001,"PER"],[1021,1026,"ORG"],[1104,1112,"PER"],[1114,1122,"PER"],[1137,1142,"ORG"],[1164,1178,"LOC"],[1221,1233,"ORG"],[1235,1242,"PER"],[1244,1254,"PER"],[1256,1265,"PER"],[1267,1280,"PER"],[1282,1293,"PER"],[1295,1311,"PER"],[1313,1330,"PER"],[1335,1344,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":8,"text":"Real Madrid have confirmed the signing of goalkeeper Kepa Arrizabalaga on a season-long loan from Chelsea. The Spanish side lost starting goalkeeper Thibaut Courtois to an ACL injury last week, just days before centre-back Eder Militao suffered the same fate. After talks over Sevilla's Yassine Bounou hit a wall, Madrid focused their offers on Kepa and have now completed a loan move for the Chelsea stopper. Kepa had been targeted by Bayern Munich and former Chelsea boss Thomas Tuchel but Madrid's interest in a loan deal moved incredibly quickly over the weekend and they have now announced his arrival. feed \"We were close and in fact we wanted to introduce Kepa today,\" Bayern CEO Jan-Christian Dreesen said on Sunday. \"But he is Spanish and he chose Real Madrid.\" Chelsea have already been active in the goalkeeper market this summer, selling Edouard Mendy to Al Ahli and replacing him with Brighton's Robert Sanchez. Sanchez was expected to compete with Kepa for the starting spot but was thrown into Mauricio Pochettino's first lineup on Sunday after Chelsea accepted Madrid's offer. As a result, Chelsea are expected to turn back to the transfer market to find a replacement for Kepa. The Blues are long-term admirers of Valencia's Giorgi Mamardashvili, who was also a target for Real Madrid. Porto's Diogo Costa is seen as too expensive at this point in the window.","label":[[0,11,"ORG"],[53,70,"PER"],[98,105,"ORG"],[149,165,"PER"],[223,235,"PER"],[277,286,"ORG"],[287,301,"PER"],[314,320,"ORG"],[345,349,"PER"],[393,400,"ORG"],[410,414,"PER"],[436,449,"ORG"],[461,468,"ORG"],[474,486,"PER"],[492,500,"ORG"],[663,667,"PER"],[676,682,"ORG"],[687,708,"PER"],[757,768,"ORG"],[771,778,"ORG"],[850,863,"PER"],[867,874,"ORG"],[898,908,"ORG"],[909,923,"PER"],[925,932,"PER"],[962,966,"PER"],[1009,1030,"PER"],[1060,1067,"ORG"],[1077,1085,"ORG"],[1106,1113,"ORG"],[1189,1193,"PER"],[1195,1204,"ORG"],[1231,1241,"ORG"],[1242,1262,"PER"],[1290,1301,"ORG"],[1303,1310,"ORG"],[1311,1322,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":9,"text":"Chelsea have finalised an agreement with Southampton to sign midfielder Romeo Lavia, 90min understands. After striking a deal over a fee with the Saints, Chelsea set about finalising the terms of a move which sources have confirmed is worth around  £58m including add-ons. Southampton director Jason Wilcox confirmed earlier on Tuesday that the two clubs were still in negotiations at that point, but just a few hours later, the Saints have shook hands with Chelsea and are bidding farewell to Lavia. Lavia is due to undergo a medical with Chelsea in the coming days ahead of putting pen to paper on another long-term contract at Stamford Bridge. The Belgian had the opportunity to join Liverpool this summer but, like Moises Caicedo, has opted to join Chelsea instead. feed Should all go to plan with his medical, Lavia will become the latest in a long list of new signings at Chelsea. Alongside Caicedo, the Blues have already recruited Axel Disasi, Christopher Nkunku, Nicolas Jackson, Lesley Ugochukwu, Angelo Gabriel, Robert Sanchez and Diego Moreira this summer, and they are not expected to finish there. Indeed, 90min understands Chelsea have agreed a deal to sign Crystal Palace midfielder Michael Olise, who has a  £35m release clause in his contract with the Eagles. The Blues are then expected to turn their attention to a new goalkeeper to replace Kepa Arrizabalaga, who has joined Real Madrid on loan, while club officials have not yet ruled out pursuing another striker as well.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[41,52,"ORG"],[72,83,"PER"],[85,90,"ORG"],[142,152,"ORG"],[154,161,"ORG"],[249,253,"MON"],[273,284,"ORG"],[294,306,"PER"],[425,435,"ORG"],[458,465,"ORG"],[494,499,"PER"],[501,506,"PER"],[540,547,"ORG"],[630,645,"LOC"],[687,696,"ORG"],[719,733,"PER"],[753,760,"ORG"],[815,820,"PER"],[878,885,"ORG"],[897,904,"PER"],[906,915,"ORG"],[939,950,"PER"],[952,970,"PER"],[972,987,"PER"],[989,1005,"PER"],[1007,1021,"PER"],[1023,1037,"PER"],[1042,1055,"PER"],[1120,1125,"ORG"],[1138,1145,"ORG"],[1173,1187,"ORG"],[1199,1212,"PER"],[1225,1229,"MON"],[1266,1276,"ORG"],[1278,1287,"ORG"],[1361,1378,"PER"],[1395,1406,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":10,"text":"Chelsea are confident that they are close to finalising a British record transfer for Brighton & Hove Albion, sources have confirmed to 90min. Liverpool had agreed a deal with Brighton to sign Caicedo on Thursday evening worth  £111m and the 21-year-old was due on Merseyside for a medical on Friday morning. However, it quickly became apparent that Caicedo was not going to travel to the north of England as he and his agents made it clear to Brighton that he would still prefer a move to Chelsea. The Blue had previously seen a number of bids rejected, the biggest of which had been worth  £80m and was still someway short of the minimum  £100m asking price required by the Seagulls. Now, whilst an agreement is not yet finalised, 90min has been informed that talks are progressing between Chelsea and Brighton and the deal is set to be worth in excess of the  £111m fee agreed with Liverpool earlier in the week. Once confirmed, it would break Chelsea's own British record which they set in January when signing Enzo Fernandez from Benfica in a deal worth  £106m 90min can also confirm that talks between Caicedo have accelerated to the point that personal terms are all finalised and the Ecuadorian is ready to put pen to paper on an eight-year contract as soon as the two clubs confirm an agreement over price is in place. feed Chelsea are hopeful that they could parade both Caicedo and Romeo Lavia, who is close to finalising move from Southampton after a  £55m fee was agreed, ahead of Sunday's Premier League clash with, ironically, Liverpool, who not only wanted Caicedo but also had multiple bids for Lavia rejected. For their part, Brighton are already moving forward with the belief that Caicedo is no longer theirs and boss Roberto De Zerbi considers him a former player. \"I have already forgotten about Moises,\" he said. \"I'm really proud of the players we have in the squad. We want to keep improving. The credit goes to the club. Bigger clubs can buy our players but they can't buy our soul or spirit. \"We don't have enough [players] yet, we need to complete the squad. I want players who want to come here. We are Brighton, we achieved a big target last year - the same as Liverpool, better than Chelsea. I would like players who are proud to play in Brighton.\"","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[86,108,"ORG"],[136,141,"ORG"],[143,152,"ORG"],[176,184,"ORG"],[193,200,"PER"],[228,233,"MON"],[265,275,"LOC"],[350,357,"PER"],[398,405,"LOC"],[444,452,"ORG"],[490,497,"ORG"],[499,507,"ORG"],[592,596,"MON"],[641,646,"MON"],[672,684,"ORG"],[733,738,"ORG"],[792,799,"ORG"],[804,812,"ORG"],[863,868,"MON"],[885,894,"ORG"],[947,956,"ORG"],[994,1001,"DAT"],[1015,1029,"PER"],[1035,1042,"ORG"],[1060,1065,"MON"],[1066,1071,"ORG"],[1108,1115,"PER"],[1333,1340,"ORG"],[1381,1388,"PER"],[1393,1404,"PER"],[1443,1454,"ORG"],[1464,1468,"MON"],[1503,1517,"ORG"],[1542,1551,"ORG"],[1573,1580,"PER"],[1612,1617,"PER"],[1644,1652,"ORG"],[1701,1708,"PER"],[1738,1754,"PER"],[1818,1824,"PER"],[2132,2140,"ORG"],[2191,2200,"ORG"],[2214,2221,"ORG"],[2269,2277,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":11,"text":"Romeo Lavia is to undergo a medical at Chelsea after turning down the chance to join Liverpool, sources have confirmed to 90min. The 19-year-old's future has been the subject of intense speculation for weeks, with a departure from Southampton expected after the club's relegation to the Championship. Chelsea and Liverpool have both been pushing hard to sign Lavia, with the two clubs also doing battle to sign Moises Caicedo from Brighton in a deal that will make the British transfer record currently held by Enzo Fernandez. And just as Caicedo has chosen to move to Stamford Bridge, Lavia has decided his future is also in west London, turning down the opportunity to work under Jurgen Klopp in the process. 90min understands that the Belgian teenager will undergo a medical with Chelsea in the next 24 hours before sealing a move that could eventually be worth  £55m to Southampton. feed Caicedo is also set to imminently put pen to paper on an eight-year contract, joining forces with Fernandez and manager Mauricio Pochettino to create one of the most expensively assembled midfields in world football. Liverpool had indicated a willingness to match Chelsea's offer for Lavia, in the hope that he would choose to join the Reds, but they have again been left disappointed in their hunt for a new defensive midfielder. Fabinho has left the club this summer to join Al Ittihad in Saudi Arabia amid a complete overhaul of Liverpool's midfield. Jordan Henderson, Naby Keita, James Milner and Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain have also moved on to pastures new, gutting the core of a side that failed to qualify for this season's Champions League. Alexis Mac Allister, Dominik Szoboszlai and Cody Gakpo started in an extremely attacking midfield three in the 1-1 draw with Chelsea on Sunday, though it was clear in that game that Liverpool need a more defensive-minded player to help protect the backline when the ball is turned over.","label":[[0,11,"PER"],[39,46,"ORG"],[85,94,"ORG"],[122,127,"ORG"],[231,242,"ORG"],[287,299,"ORG"],[301,308,"ORG"],[313,322,"ORG"],[359,364,"PER"],[411,425,"PER"],[431,439,"ORG"],[511,525,"PER"],[539,546,"PER"],[569,584,"LOC"],[586,591,"PER"],[631,637,"LOC"],[682,694,"PER"],[711,716,"ORG"],[783,790,"ORG"],[866,870,"MON"],[874,885,"ORG"],[892,899,"PER"],[990,999,"PER"],[1012,1031,"PER"],[1109,1118,"ORG"],[1156,1165,"ORG"],[1176,1181,"PER"],[1224,1232,"ORG"],[1323,1330,"PER"],[1369,1379,"ORG"],[1383,1395,"LOC"],[1424,1435,"ORG"],[1446,1462,"PER"],[1464,1474,"PER"],[1476,1488,"PER"],[1493,1516,"PER"],[1621,1637,"ORG"],[1639,1658,"PER"],[1660,1678,"PER"],[1683,1693,"PER"],[1764,1771,"ORG"],[1821,1830,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":12,"text":"Talented Chelsea youngster Cesare Casadei has joined Championship side Leicester City on a season-long loan.  Casadei spent the 2022\/23 campaign on loan in the same division with Reading, making 15 appearances and scoring one goal.  The midfielder has recently caught the eye much more at Under-20 level for Italy, winning the Golden Ball and Golden Boot awards for his stunning performances in the FIFA Under-20 World Cup. In Italy's run to the final - a final they'd lose to Uruguay 1-0 - Casadei managed a thoroughly impressive seven goals in seven games.  With Chelsea confirming the British record signing of Moises Caicedo this week and also closing in on Romeo Lavia from Southampton, the Italian midfielder has now secured a loan to Leicester in order to get some game time under his belt.  feed Speaking to the Foxes' official website after making the move, Casadei said: \"I feel really good. I   m really happy to be here, I   m excited and I can   t wait to get started. Obviously, Leicester is a big team so I   m here to win and to do as well as possible to fight and to work hard for this team.\" In a statement released by Chelsea, the club's co-sporting directors Laurence Stewart and Paul Winstanley added: \"This loan move is the perfect opportunity for Cesare to continue his progression as an exciting, young footballer. \"We   re excited to see how he performs under Enzo Maresca at Leicester and look forward to watching him continue on this journey.\"","label":[[9,16,"ORG"],[27,41,"PER"],[53,65,"ORG"],[71,85,"ORG"],[110,117,"PER"],[128,135,"DAT"],[179,186,"ORG"],[308,313,"ORG"],[399,422,"ORG"],[427,434,"ORG"],[477,484,"ORG"],[491,498,"PER"],[565,572,"ORG"],[614,628,"PER"],[662,673,"PER"],[679,690,"ORG"],[741,750,"ORG"],[816,826,"ORG"],[867,874,"PER"],[993,1002,"ORG"],[1137,1144,"ORG"],[1179,1195,"PER"],[1200,1215,"PER"],[1270,1276,"PER"],[1385,1397,"PER"],[1401,1410,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":13,"text":"Jurgen Klopp has confirmed he does not expect Liverpool to part ways with midfielder Thiago Alcantara this summer. Thiago is the latest Liverpool midfielder to attract interest from Saudi Arabia, with reports suggesting a reunion with Roberto Firmino at Al Ahli could be on the cards. Liverpool have already sold both Jordan Henderson and Fabinho to Saudi Arabia, while James Milner, Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain and Naby Keita have departed on free transfers, leaving Klopp's side a little light in midfield. As a result, there are no plans to offload Thiago, who is back in training after recovery from a hip injury. \"He   s now training, he came in and asked about his role and we spoke,\" Klopp told his pre-match press conference before Liverpool's opening Premier League game of the new season. \"[He   s a] super experienced player, he stepped up in that department. He has only been in team training for a week but very vocal, he is going to be very helpful for us.\" feed Liverpool continue to search for midfield reinforcements and have been in talks over both Brighton's Moises Caicedo and Southampton's Romeo Lavia. A British record deal of  £111m was agreed for the former but interest from Chelsea has proven to be a real problem. The Blues had been chasing Caicedo all summer and the Ecuador international is understood to be prioritising a move to Stamford Bridge as a result. Meanwhile, Chelsea are also closing in on a deal for Lavia, for whom Liverpool had three bids rejected before igniting their pursuit of Caicedo. Liverpool's third offer for Lavia stood at  £46m - short of Southampton's  £50m asking price - but Chelsea are pursuing an agreement which would be worth  £55m. Alexis Mac Allister and Dominik Szoboszlai have already arrived at Anfield, adding significant creative ability to Liverpool's ranks.","label":[[0,12,"PER"],[46,55,"ORG"],[85,101,"PER"],[115,121,"PER"],[136,145,"ORG"],[182,194,"LOC"],[235,250,"PER"],[254,261,"ORG"],[285,294,"ORG"],[318,334,"PER"],[339,346,"PER"],[350,362,"LOC"],[370,382,"PER"],[384,407,"PER"],[412,422,"PER"],[464,471,"PER"],[548,554,"PER"],[687,692,"PER"],[736,747,"ORG"],[756,770,"ORG"],[973,982,"ORG"],[1063,1073,"ORG"],[1074,1088,"PER"],[1093,1106,"ORG"],[1107,1118,"PER"],[1146,1151,"MON"],[1196,1203,"ORG"],[1237,1246,"ORG"],[1264,1271,"PER"],[1291,1298,"ORG"],[1356,1371,"LOC"],[1396,1403,"ORG"],[1438,1443,"PER"],[1454,1463,"ORG"],[1521,1528,"PER"],[1530,1541,"ORG"],[1558,1563,"PER"],[1574,1578,"MON"],[1590,1603,"ORG"],[1605,1609,"MON"],[1629,1636,"ORG"],[1685,1689,"MON"],[1691,1710,"PER"],[1715,1733,"PER"],[1758,1765,"LOC"],[1806,1817,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":14,"text":"Manchester United have announced they have reached an agreement with Fenerbahce for the transfer of Fred. The Brazil midfielder will end his five-year stay at Old Trafford following a medical and the finalisation of personal terms. Man Utd will receive a fee in the region of  £13m for Fred. A club statement on Friday evening read: \"Manchester United can confirm an agreement in principle has been reached with Fenerbahce for the transfer of Fred. \"The Brazil international is set for a switch to the Turkish Super Lig, subject to a medical, agreeing personal terms and receiving international clearance to process the move. \"Our no.17 is scheduled to fly out to Istanbul on Saturday, in order to take his medical tests.\" feed They added: \"The 30-year-old leaves so many positive memories from his time at Old Trafford, where he has been a hugely popular individual, both as a person and as a player. \"Everybody at the club would like to wish the very best of luck to Fred for the future, as we await confirmation that the deal is completed.\" 90min has extensively reported in recent weeks that Man Utd have been looking to shift Fred and fellow midfielder Donny van de Beek in order to fund a move for Fiorentina's Sofyan Amrabat. The Red Devils remain in talks with Real Sociedad regarding an initial loan for Van de Beek.","label":[[0,17,"ORG"],[69,79,"ORG"],[100,104,"PER"],[110,116,"ORG"],[159,171,"LOC"],[232,239,"ORG"],[277,281,"MON"],[286,290,"PER"],[334,351,"ORG"],[412,422,"ORG"],[443,447,"PER"],[454,460,"ORG"],[502,519,"ORG"],[664,672,"LOC"],[807,819,"LOC"],[969,973,"PER"],[1044,1049,"ORG"],[1096,1103,"ORG"],[1131,1135,"PER"],[1158,1175,"PER"],[1204,1216,"ORG"],[1217,1231,"PER"],[1233,1247,"ORG"],[1269,1282,"ORG"],[1313,1324,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":15,"text":"Liverpool manager Jurgen Klopp has aimed a dig at Chelsea's transfer business amid the races to sign midfielders Moises Caicedo and Romeo Lavia.  Liverpool have been keen to add another midfielder to their ranks all summer having let Jordan Henderson, Fabinho, Naby Keita, James Milner and Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain all the leave the club, and recently saw a  £111m bid accepted by Brighton and Hove Albion for the talented Caicedo.   However, Caicedo's preference to move to Stamford Bridge has invited Chelsea back into the race and 90min understands that Brighton have now accepted a British record  £115m bid from the Blues for the player, with Caicedo now set to put pen to paper on an eight-year deal at Chelsea.  Along with Caicedo, Liverpool have also faced stiff competition from Chelsea for their other primary midfield target Romeo Lavia. The Reds saw three bids rejected before Chelsea entered the race, initially bidding  £48m before offering  £55m. 90min reported on Sunday that Liverpool are now willing to match Chelsea's bid in the hope of signing Lavia from Southampton. feed When asked by Sky Sports about the ongoing transfer battles between Liverpool and Chelsea after the clubs' 1-1 draw at Stamford Bridge, Klopp was keen to aim a thinly-veiled dig at the Blues for their spending. \"Where   s the camera? No [I cannot say anything]. Oh, that [new signings] is what the Chelsea manager wants, and usually they get it! I   ve got nothing to say about it to be honest,\" he said. \"I   m sorry.\" Once the Caicedo signing is confirmed, Chelsea will have spent over  £800m on new players since Todd Boehly took over ownership of the club. This summer alone, the Blues will have spent nearly  £300m on eight players for new manager Mauricio Pochettino. ","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[18,30,"PER"],[50,59,"ORG"],[113,127,"PER"],[132,143,"PER"],[146,155,"ORG"],[234,250,"PER"],[252,259,"PER"],[261,271,"PER"],[273,285,"PER"],[290,313,"PER"],[358,363,"MON"],[380,404,"ORG"],[422,429,"PER"],[442,451,"PER"],[474,489,"LOC"],[502,509,"ORG"],[533,538,"ORG"],[556,564,"ORG"],[601,606,"MON"],[616,625,"ORG"],[647,654,"PER"],[708,715,"ORG"],[729,736,"PER"],[738,747,"ORG"],[787,794,"ORG"],[835,846,"PER"],[848,856,"ORG"],[888,895,"ORG"],[933,937,"MON"],[955,959,"MON"],[961,966,"ORG"],[991,1000,"ORG"],[1026,1035,"ORG"],[1063,1068,"PER"],[1074,1085,"ORG"],[1106,1116,"ORG"],[1160,1169,"ORG"],[1174,1181,"ORG"],[1211,1226,"LOC"],[1228,1233,"PER"],[1273,1282,"ORG"],[1390,1397,"ORG"],[1521,1528,"PER"],[1551,1558,"ORG"],[1581,1586,"MON"],[1608,1619,"PER"],[1672,1681,"ORG"],[1706,1711,"MON"],[1745,1764,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":16,"text":"Aston Villa are close to finalising a deal with Galatasaray for Italy international Nicolo Zaniolo, sources have confirmed to 90min. The 24-year-old attacker only moved to Turkey in February after a January transfer from Roma to Bournemouth collapsed. Instead, he signed a four-and-half-year deal with the Istanbul giants. Zaniolo helped Gala to their first Turkish Super Lig title in four years by scoring five goals in ten league games, but now he is set to leave the club just six months after arriving. Villa have been looking to find a replacement for the injured Emi Buendia and Zaniolo has been picked out by president of football operations Monchi and head coach Unai Emery. Indeed, Emery has already spoken about the qualities of Zaniolo and what he coud bring to his side.  feed \"Zaniolo is not a striker. He is versatile,\" the boss said. \"He can play as a striker, a number seven or a number 10 and he is one of those on our list, with the qualities he has, to help us.\"","label":[[0,11,"ORG"],[48,59,"ORG"],[64,69,"ORG"],[84,98,"PER"],[126,131,"ORG"],[172,178,"LOC"],[182,190,"DAT"],[199,206,"DAT"],[221,225,"ORG"],[229,240,"ORG"],[306,314,"LOC"],[323,330,"PER"],[338,342,"ORG"],[358,375,"ORG"],[507,512,"ORG"],[569,580,"PER"],[585,592,"PER"],[649,655,"PER"],[671,681,"PER"],[691,696,"PER"],[739,746,"PER"],[790,797,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":17,"text":"Brighton & Hove Albion have opened talks with Lille over the transfer of midfield starlet Carlos Baleba, 90min understands. Baleba is regarded as one of the top young midfield prospects in Ligue 1 and Brighton are one of several sides who have been following him for months. 90min revealed in March that they were one of a number of Premier League clubs who were scouting the highly-rated teenager. With Moises Caicedo ready to depart the club for Chelsea for a British-record  £115m fee, Brighton are looking for his replacement and they have opted for Baleba. feed Cameroon-born Baleba has been with Lille since 2022 when they picked him up from the Ecole de Football des Brasseries academy. He quickly progressed into the first-team and helped replace Amadou Onana last summer after he joined Everton. Now, Baleba is set to follow in Onana's foot-steps to the Premier League. Sources have confirmed to 90min that Lille are looking for a fee of around    30m ( £25.8m) and a deal is now close between the two clubs, with his representatives finalising personal terms. Baleba featured in Lille's opening game of the season on Friday as they claimed a 1-1 draw at Nice, but that is set to be his final appearance for the club ahead of a move to Brighton this week.","label":[[0,22,"ORG"],[46,51,"ORG"],[90,103,"PER"],[105,110,"ORG"],[124,130,"PER"],[189,196,"ORG"],[201,209,"ORG"],[275,280,"ORG"],[293,298,"DAT"],[333,347,"ORG"],[404,418,"PER"],[448,455,"ORG"],[478,483,"MON"],[489,497,"ORG"],[554,560,"PER"],[581,587,"PER"],[602,607,"ORG"],[614,618,"DAT"],[652,684,"ORG"],[755,767,"PER"],[796,803,"ORG"],[810,816,"PER"],[837,844,"PER"],[863,877,"ORG"],[905,910,"ORG"],[916,921,"ORG"],[957,960,"MON"],[963,969,"MON"],[1070,1076,"PER"],[1089,1096,"ORG"],[1164,1168,"ORG"],[1245,1253,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":18,"text":"West Ham United have completed the signing of Southampton captain James Ward-Prowse for an undisclosed fee. The 28-year-old has inked a four-year contract at London Stadium to end an association with Southampton that dates all the way back to 2003, joining David Moyes' side after the latter's relegation to the Championship. \"I   m buzzing to be here at West Ham United. It   s great to be here and I   m looking forward to getting going,\"  Ward-Prowse told the club's official website. \"From the outside looking in, this is a Club that has been on the rise for a number of years now and coming off the success in the UEFA Europa Conference League last year, you can feel there is real momentum around this Club. It   s great to be a part of it and I can   t wait to play my role in the games to come. \"When I think about my game, it is based on hard work, graft, and giving 100%. West Ham United has always been a Club that has epitomises that. You can feel that from the fans and you can see it in the players who are here and the lads that have come through the Academy too. \"I feel as though I will fit straight in and I can promise I will give my all for this football club in my time here.\" feed Capped 11 times by England, Ward-Prowse made 410 appearances on the south coast in all competitions, scoring 55 goals while laying on the same amount for his teammates, with his leadership skills among the traits praised by Moyes. \"I   m delighted to bring a player of James    quality and experience to West Ham United,\"  the Scot said of Ward-Prowse's arrival.    He's performed to a very high level in the Premier League over the last decade, constantly producing good numbers season after season. \"His leadership qualities are obviously another huge plus for us     he   ll be a big voice for us, someone who drives the team on from the middle of the pitch. We   re excited to get him up and running, for what will be another busy season on both the domestic and European front.\" Ward-Prowse will wear the number 7 shirt at West Ham, vacated by Gianluca Scamacca following his  £26m move to Atalanta, and although the fee is undisclosed, 90min understands that around  £30m has been parted with to facilitate the move.","label":[[0,15,"ORG"],[46,57,"ORG"],[66,83,"PER"],[158,172,"LOC"],[200,211,"ORG"],[243,247,"DAT"],[257,269,"PER"],[312,324,"ORG"],[355,370,"ORG"],[442,453,"PER"],[619,648,"ORG"],[876,880,"PCT"],[882,897,"ORG"],[1222,1229,"ORG"],[1231,1242,"PER"],[1427,1432,"PER"],[1472,1477,"PER"],[1507,1522,"ORG"],[1543,1556,"PER"],[1612,1626,"ORG"],[1987,1998,"PER"],[2031,2039,"ORG"],[2052,2069,"PER"],[2085,2089,"MON"],[2098,2106,"ORG"],[2145,2150,"ORG"],[2176,2180,"MON"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":19,"text":"Neymar has agreed personal terms with Saudi Arabian side Al Hilal as he inches closer to a move away from Paris Saint-Germain, 90min understands. The Brazil international was offered the chance to move to the Middle East earlier this summer when Al Hilal made him their top alternative to PSG teammate Kylian Mbappe, but Neymar initially rejected the offer. However, sources have now confirmed to 90min that Neymar has given his approval to joining Al Hilal, who are back in pursuit of the Brazilian after their attemps to land Napoli striker Victor Osimhen fell flat, and has agreed the terms of an eye-watering contract worth around    220,000 ( £189,000) per day. PSG, who have been looking for buyers for Neymar, have welcomed interest from the Saudi Public Investment Fund (PIF) and are understood to have accepted a    90m ( £77.6m) bid from Al Hilal to get the deal done. All parties are now finalising a move which is expected to be formally completed in the coming days. feed Saudi sources have laughed off suggestions Neymar could be loaned out after joining Al Hilal amid rumours of potential interest from Barcelona. Neymar's expected departure is the latest event in a tumultuous summer for PSG, who also remain in talks with Al Hilal over the potential sale of midfielder Marco Verratti. Lionel Messi left on a free transfer to join Inter Miami and it appeared as though he would be followed out the door by Kylian Mbappe who, after confirming he did not plan to trigger the extension in his contract, was frozen out of the first team. After being omitted from Luis Enrique's first matchday squad, however, Mbappe was welcomed back into the squad and the 24-year-old is in line to make his first appearance of the season against Toulouse on Saturday.","label":[[0,6,"PER"],[57,65,"ORG"],[106,125,"ORG"],[150,156,"ORG"],[209,220,"LOC"],[246,254,"ORG"],[289,292,"ORG"],[302,315,"PER"],[321,327,"PER"],[397,402,"ORG"],[408,414,"PER"],[449,457,"ORG"],[528,534,"ORG"],[543,557,"PER"],[638,645,"MON"],[648,656,"MON"],[667,670,"ORG"],[709,715,"PER"],[749,783,"ORG"],[825,828,"MON"],[831,837,"MON"],[848,856,"ORG"],[1028,1034,"PER"],[1069,1077,"ORG"],[1118,1127,"ORG"],[1129,1137,"PER"],[1204,1207,"ORG"],[1239,1246,"ORG"],[1286,1300,"PER"],[1302,1314,"PER"],[1347,1358,"ORG"],[1422,1435,"PER"],[1575,1589,"PER"],[1621,1627,"PER"],[1743,1751,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":20,"text":"Everton have confirmed the signing of wide midfielder Jack Harrison from Leeds United on a season-long loan deal.  Harrison had yet to feature for Leeds since their relegation to the Championship, missing the club's first two games of the season amid injury and uncertainty about his future, and was also a target for Unai Emery's Aston Villa. But the former Manchester City man has secured a move back to the Premier League with Everton, with a club statement saying of his arrival: \"Everton have completed the signing of forward Jack Harrison on a season-long loan from Leeds United. \"The 26-year-old passed his medical with the Club yesterday before completing the necessary paperwork this morning. He will now continue his rehabilitation from a minor hip injury before being available for Sean Dyche   s squad. \"He becomes Everton   s fourth signing of the summer transfer window following the arrivals of forward Arnaut Danjuma, defender Ashley Young and striker Youssef Chermiti.\" Harrison had been one of Leeds' standout performers during their three-year stay in the Premier League, scoring 21 league goals for the club. Though he will not take to the field immediately, Everton will hope he can make a swift impact and help the Toffees kick on under Sean Dyche.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[54,66,"PER"],[73,85,"ORG"],[115,123,"PER"],[147,152,"ORG"],[183,195,"ORG"],[318,330,"PER"],[331,342,"ORG"],[359,374,"ORG"],[410,424,"ORG"],[430,437,"ORG"],[485,492,"ORG"],[531,544,"PER"],[572,584,"ORG"],[793,803,"PER"],[827,834,"ORG"],[918,932,"PER"],[943,955,"PER"],[968,984,"PER"],[987,995,"PER"],[1012,1018,"ORG"],[1075,1089,"ORG"],[1179,1186,"ORG"],[1233,1244,"ORG"],[1259,1269,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":21,"text":"90min  rounds up the latest  transfer news, rumours and gossip circulating around the world... Kylian Mbappe has reached an agreement with Paris Saint-Germain to extend his contract for a further 12 months to ensure he does not leave the club for free next summer. (RMC Sport) Real Madrid continue to hunt for a new goalkeeper and have expressed an interest in Porto's Diogo Costa, who will only be allowed to leave if his release clause of    75m is triggered. (Fichajes) The interest in Costa comes after Real Madrid saw a loan offer for Valencia's Giorgi Mamardashvili rejected. (COPE) Liverpool,  Bayern Munich  and  PSG  are all interested in  PSV Eindhoven midfielder Ibrahim Sangare. (ESPN) Manchester United have seen an opening bid for Bayern Munich defender Benjamin Pavard rejected by the German club. (Sky Germany) Despite Chelsea declining a swap deal involving Dusan Vlahovic, Juventus remain in talks with the Blues over signing striker Romelu Lukaku. (Corriere dello Sport) manual Barcelona are considering offering winger Ansu Fati to Atletico Madrid in a swap deal for Portuguese forward Joao Felix, but such a bid is only expected to be made towards the end of the transfer window. (Helena Condis Edo) A formal bid from Barcelona is also expected to be made for Manchester City full-back Joao Cancelo, who will be given the chance to move to Catalonia on loan with an option for a permanent deal. (Fabrizio Romano) Man City will consider making a move for Crystal Palace midfielder Michael Olise if they fail to get a deal for West Ham United's Lucas Paqueta over the line. (Football Insider) Tottenham are considering a move for Arsenal striker Folarin Balogun after Harry Kane's departure to Bayern Munich. (Gazzetta dello Sport) With a move for Neymar inching closer, Saudi Arabian side Al Hilal have also reignited their interest in Fulham striker Aleksandar Mitrovic. (Mail)","label":[[0,5,"ORG"],[95,108,"PER"],[139,158,"ORG"],[266,275,"ORG"],[277,288,"ORG"],[361,368,"ORG"],[369,380,"PER"],[444,447,"MON"],[463,471,"ORG"],[489,494,"PER"],[507,518,"ORG"],[540,550,"ORG"],[551,571,"PER"],[583,587,"ORG"],[589,598,"ORG"],[601,614,"ORG"],[621,624,"ORG"],[649,662,"ORG"],[674,689,"PER"],[692,696,"ORG"],[698,715,"ORG"],[745,758,"ORG"],[768,783,"PER"],[814,825,"ORG"],[835,842,"ORG"],[875,889,"PER"],[891,899,"ORG"],[921,930,"ORG"],[952,965,"PER"],[968,988,"ORG"],[997,1006,"ORG"],[1039,1048,"PER"],[1052,1067,"ORG"],[1106,1116,"PER"],[1202,1219,"PER"],[1239,1248,"ORG"],[1281,1296,"ORG"],[1307,1319,"PER"],[1361,1370,"LOC"],[1417,1432,"PER"],[1434,1442,"ORG"],[1475,1489,"ORG"],[1501,1514,"PER"],[1546,1563,"ORG"],[1564,1577,"PER"],[1594,1610,"ORG"],[1612,1621,"ORG"],[1649,1656,"ORG"],[1665,1680,"PER"],[1687,1699,"PER"],[1713,1725,"ORG"],[1729,1749,"ORG"],[1767,1773,"PER"],[1809,1817,"ORG"],[1856,1862,"ORG"],[1871,1890,"PER"],[1893,1897,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":22,"text":"Brighton and Hove Albion CEO Paul Barber has confessed Moises Caicedo's decision to reject a transfer to Liverpool in favour of joining Chelsea came as a surprise. Chelsea confirmed the  £115m signing of Caicedo on Monday after a tense weekend which began with Liverpool coming out of nowhere to agree a fee of  £111m to sign the Ecuador international. However, Caicedo soon made it clear that he would prefer a move to Stamford Bridge, urging Brighton to reopen negotiations with Chelsea and ultimately sealing the move he was looking for. Barber admitted to talkSPORT that Caicedo's stance left Brighton in an unexpected and \"difficult\" situation as they tried to find an outcome which satisfied everyone. feed \"Liverpool are a fantastic club, you   d imagine anyone would be running up the M6 for the chance to play at Anfield, but for whatever reason, Moises and his advisors decided London was their preferred destination,\" he said. \"In that situation we   re in a difficult position; we   ve negotiated a British record deal deal and spent several days working with Liverpool, who were were professional throughout. \"At that point [when Caicedo rejected the move], we   re out of the loop, it is all between the player and Liverpool. When it became clear he isn   t going to be joining Liverpool, we have to go into a different mode, we then have to do it all again, which we did. \"We started working with Chelsea, and we had to protect our own interests which is the player. We did that and now Moises goes on to the next step in his career.\" Liverpool and Chelsea have also butted heads over Southampton midfielder Romeo Lavia who, like Caicedo, has opted to move to Stamford Bridge this summer.","label":[[0,24,"ORG"],[29,40,"PER"],[55,71,"PER"],[105,114,"ORG"],[136,143,"ORG"],[164,171,"ORG"],[187,192,"MON"],[204,211,"PER"],[261,270,"ORG"],[312,317,"MON"],[330,337,"ORG"],[362,369,"PER"],[420,435,"LOC"],[444,452,"ORG"],[481,488,"ORG"],[541,547,"PER"],[560,569,"ORG"],[575,584,"PER"],[597,605,"ORG"],[714,723,"ORG"],[822,829,"LOC"],[856,862,"PER"],[888,894,"LOC"],[1072,1081,"ORG"],[1143,1150,"PER"],[1229,1238,"ORG"],[1292,1301,"ORG"],[1412,1419,"ORG"],[1502,1508,"PER"],[1550,1559,"ORG"],[1564,1571,"ORG"],[1600,1611,"ORG"],[1623,1634,"PER"],[1645,1652,"PER"],[1675,1690,"LOC"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":23,"text":"Paris Saint-Germain have confirmed that Kylian Mbappe has been allowed to return to first-team training after \"constructive and positive discussions\" regarding his future.  90min reported earlier this week that Mbappe had reiterated his desire to stay at PSG beyond this summer despite not taking up his option to trigger a clause which would extend his current contract at the club until the summer of 2025. That decision not to trigger an extension had led to PSG shopping the superstar forward around this summer due to the fear of losing him as a free agent next summer. The Ligue 1 giants accepted a world record offer  of  £257m (   300m) from Al Hilal last month, but despite proposing a gargantuan contract offer to Mbappe, the PIF-backed Saudi Pro League side were  unable to persuade the France star to enter negotiations. On top of trying to sell Mbappe, PSG had also banished the player from first-team training and even refused to select him for their recent pre-season tour of Japan.  manual Now, however, the 2018 World Cup winner is back in the first-team squad and back in training with his teammates after what the club have described as positive talks regarding the player's future which took place on Saturday.  A club statement on the news reads: \"After very constructive and positive discussions between Paris Saint-Germain and Kylian Mbappe before the PSG - Lorient match, this Saturday 12th August, the player was reinstated in first-team training this morning.\"  Mbappe was in the stands on Saturday for PSG's 0-0 draw with Lorient in their Ligue 1 season opener, sitting alongside new teammate Ousmane Dembele, whom the club officially confirmed the signing of on Saturday morning. The pair could feature together for the first time at club level next Saturday when Luis Enrique's team take on Toulouse.","label":[[0,19,"ORG"],[40,53,"PER"],[173,178,"ORG"],[211,217,"PER"],[255,258,"ORG"],[403,407,"DAT"],[462,465,"ORG"],[579,586,"ORG"],[629,634,"MON"],[639,643,"MON"],[650,658,"ORG"],[724,730,"PER"],[747,763,"ORG"],[798,804,"ORG"],[858,864,"PER"],[866,869,"ORG"],[991,996,"LOC"],[1024,1028,"DAT"],[1029,1038,"ORG"],[1326,1345,"ORG"],[1350,1363,"PER"],[1375,1378,"ORG"],[1381,1388,"ORG"],[1410,1421,"DAT"],[1488,1494,"PER"],[1529,1534,"ORG"],[1549,1556,"ORG"],[1566,1573,"ORG"],[1620,1635,"PER"],[1792,1806,"PER"],[1820,1828,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":24,"text":"90min  rounds up the latest  transfer news, rumours and gossip circulating around the world... West Ham have called off their move for Harry Maguire despite agreeing a  £30m fee with Manchester United. The England defender wanted a severance payment of around  £7m in order to depart Old Trafford and accept a lower wage packet at London Stadium. (Guardian) Manchester United would have needed to sign a replacement for Maguire had he chose to leave but they would have been left short of time to do so this window. (The Athletic) Despite reports suggesting otherwise, Everton have not received a bid from Manchester United for midfielder Amadou Onana, though would demand a huge transfer fee in order to sell the Belgian. (Liverpool Echo) Chelsea have agreed a  £58m fee with Southampton for Romeo Lavia as Todd Boehly's spending during his time as owner nears the  £1bn mark. (The Athletic) Manchester City will ramp up their interest in Jeremy Doku once they formalise a new bid for Lucas Paqueta. (Fabrizio Romano) manual Barcelona recently knocked back an approach from Manchester City for 16-year-old wonderkid Lamine Yamal. City had planned to loan him out to Barca's Catalan neighbours Girona. (Mundo Deportivo) Al Nassr are exploring a shock move for Liverpool goalkeeper Alisson, who is believed to be open to a move to Saudi Arabia. (Foot Mercato) In terms of incomings, Liverpool are believed to have a six-player shortlist to fill their hole in defensive midfield after losing out on Romeo Lavia and Moises Caicedo to Chelsea. Fulham's Joao Palhinha and Crystal Palace's Cheick Doucoure are towards the top of that list. (Daily Mail) Real Madrid are eyeing Arsenal centre-back Gabriel Magalhaes as a replacement for Eder Militao, who recently sustained an ACL injury. (PL Brasil) Tottenham plan to sell Eric Dier and bring in a new centre-back and star midfielder before the end of the transfer window. (Football Insider)","label":[[0,5,"ORG"],[95,103,"ORG"],[135,148,"PER"],[169,173,"MON"],[183,200,"ORG"],[206,213,"ORG"],[261,264,"MON"],[284,296,"LOC"],[331,345,"LOC"],[348,356,"ORG"],[358,375,"ORG"],[420,427,"PER"],[517,529,"ORG"],[569,576,"ORG"],[606,623,"ORG"],[639,651,"PER"],[724,738,"ORG"],[740,747,"ORG"],[762,767,"MON"],[777,788,"ORG"],[793,804,"PER"],[808,821,"PER"],[867,871,"MON"],[879,891,"ORG"],[893,908,"ORG"],[940,951,"PER"],[986,999,"PER"],[1002,1017,"PER"],[1026,1035,"ORG"],[1075,1090,"ORG"],[1117,1129,"PER"],[1131,1135,"ORG"],[1167,1174,"ORG"],[1194,1200,"ORG"],[1203,1218,"ORG"],[1220,1228,"ORG"],[1260,1269,"ORG"],[1281,1288,"PER"],[1330,1342,"LOC"],[1345,1357,"ORG"],[1382,1391,"ORG"],[1497,1508,"PER"],[1513,1527,"PER"],[1531,1538,"ORG"],[1540,1548,"ORG"],[1549,1562,"PER"],[1567,1583,"ORG"],[1584,1599,"PER"],[1635,1645,"ORG"],[1647,1658,"ORG"],[1670,1677,"ORG"],[1690,1707,"PER"],[1729,1741,"PER"],[1782,1791,"ORG"],[1793,1802,"ORG"],[1816,1825,"PER"],[1917,1933,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":25,"text":"90min  rounds up the latest  transfer news, rumours and gossip circulating around the world... Neymar has agreed a two-year contract worth    13m ( £11.2m) per season to return to Barcelona but will only be able to make the move if Paris Saint-Germain agree to terminate his contract. (El Chiringuito) Barcelona have also reignited their pursuit of Manchester City full-back Joao Cancelo. (Fabrizio Romano) Kepa Arrizabalaga has informed Chelsea that he wants to be allowed to join Bayern Munich this summer. The German side have offered to take Kepa on loan with an option to buy. (Sky Germany) Chelsea also plan to step up their interest in Crystal Palace winger Michael Olise and continue to track Ajax's Mohammed Kudus. (The Guardian) Eintracht Frankfurt do not believe they will be able to keep hold of striker Randal Kolo Muani, with PSG pushing very hard to get a deal done. (Sport1) With Harry Kane's move to Bayern Munich now complete, Tottenham have made contact with Gent over Nigerian striker Gift Orban, with a    30m ( £25.9m) bid potential on the cards. (Sacha Tavolieri) Tottenham have also expressed an interest in Arsenal striker Folarin Balogun. (Gazzetta dello Sport) manual Manchester United have added Everton midfielder Amadou Onana to their list of potential targets. (Mail) After failing with a  £70m bid, Manchester City are preparing a fresh offer for West Ham United midfielder Lucas Paqueta. (Football Insider) West Ham will demand over  £90m to part ways with Brazil international Paqueta. (Telegraph) The latest goalkeeper to be added to Real Madrid's shortlist is Leeds' Illan Meslier, who is seen as an affordable target. (SPORT) Fluminense have warned Liverpool they will not sell midfielder Andre Trindade after reaching the quarter-finals of the Copa Libertadores, insisting the 22-year-old will not leave until January at the earliest. (Globo)","label":[[0,5,"ORG"],[95,101,"PER"],[142,145,"MON"],[148,154,"MON"],[180,189,"ORG"],[232,251,"ORG"],[286,300,"ORG"],[302,311,"ORG"],[349,364,"ORG"],[375,387,"PER"],[390,405,"PER"],[407,424,"PER"],[438,445,"ORG"],[482,495,"ORG"],[546,550,"PER"],[583,594,"ORG"],[596,603,"ORG"],[643,657,"ORG"],[665,678,"PER"],[701,707,"ORG"],[708,722,"PER"],[725,737,"ORG"],[739,758,"ORG"],[816,833,"PER"],[840,843,"ORG"],[883,889,"ORG"],[896,908,"PER"],[917,930,"ORG"],[945,954,"ORG"],[978,982,"ORG"],[1005,1015,"PER"],[1027,1030,"MON"],[1033,1039,"MON"],[1070,1085,"PER"],[1087,1096,"ORG"],[1132,1139,"ORG"],[1148,1163,"PER"],[1166,1186,"ORG"],[1195,1212,"ORG"],[1224,1231,"ORG"],[1243,1255,"PER"],[1293,1297,"ORG"],[1321,1325,"MON"],[1331,1346,"ORG"],[1379,1394,"ORG"],[1406,1419,"PER"],[1422,1438,"ORG"],[1440,1448,"ORG"],[1467,1471,"MON"],[1490,1496,"ORG"],[1511,1518,"PER"],[1521,1530,"ORG"],[1569,1582,"ORG"],[1596,1602,"ORG"],[1603,1616,"PER"],[1656,1661,"ORG"],[1663,1673,"ORG"],[1686,1695,"ORG"],[1726,1740,"PER"],[1782,1799,"ORG"],[1848,1855,"DAT"],[1874,1879,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":26,"text":"Real Madrid are prepared to end their pursuit of Sevilla goalkeeper Yassine Bounou after seeing his asking price raised, 90min understands, with Chelsea's Kepa Arrizabalaga now among the club's top targets. Madrid lost usual starter Thibaut Courtois to an ACL injury earlier this week, with the Belgian stopper set to spend the majority of the coming campaign on the sidelines as a result. Sevilla's Yassine Bounou was initially targeted as a replacement after an asking price of    20m ( £17.3m) was quoted, but sources have confirmed to 90min that Sevilla are now demanding upwards of    30m (25.9m) and Madrid are prepared to walk away as a result. Club officials have drawn up a long list of potential targets, including former Manchester United star David de Gea, but further contact has been made with Kepa as Madrid seek to explore all their options. Kepa has been targeted by Bayern Munich this week as the German side seek to replace their own injured goalkeeper, Manuel Neuer, but Madrid are now exploring a rival bid for the Chelsea man. feed Chelsea have already been active in the goalkeeper market this summer, selling Edouard Mendy to Al Ahli and replacing him with Robert Sanchez of Brighton, but the interest in Kepa has seen them reignite their search for a new stopper. Long-term target Giorgi Mamardashvili of Valencia remains on Chelsea's wish list, while the Blues are also known to have considered their own move for De Gea, who is available as a free agent following his departure from United. Porto's Diogo Costa has plenty of admirers at Stamford Bridge but is understood to be too expensive for the Blues, who are locked in talks over a double deal for Brighton's Moises Caicedo and Southampton's Romeo Lavia that could cost in excess of  £160m. Madrid are relaxed about their quest for a new stopper, believing there are plenty of options available to them. Leeds United's Illan Meslier has also been added to the shortlist as the Spanish side continue their search. Publicly, manager Carlo Ancelotti has put his faith in usual deputy Andriy Lunin, who is expected to start in goal for Madrid against Athletic Club on Saturday, but a move for a new goalkeeper is expected to be made soon enough.","label":[[0,11,"ORG"],[49,56,"ORG"],[68,82,"PER"],[121,126,"ORG"],[145,154,"ORG"],[155,172,"PER"],[207,213,"ORG"],[233,249,"PER"],[390,399,"ORG"],[400,414,"PER"],[483,486,"MON"],[489,495,"MON"],[539,544,"ORG"],[550,557,"ORG"],[590,593,"MON"],[595,600,"MON"],[606,612,"ORG"],[732,749,"ORG"],[755,767,"PER"],[808,812,"PER"],[816,822,"ORG"],[858,862,"PER"],[884,897,"ORG"],[973,985,"PER"],[991,997,"ORG"],[1036,1043,"ORG"],[1054,1061,"ORG"],[1133,1146,"PER"],[1150,1157,"ORG"],[1181,1195,"PER"],[1199,1207,"ORG"],[1229,1233,"PER"],[1306,1326,"PER"],[1330,1338,"ORG"],[1350,1359,"ORG"],[1377,1386,"ORG"],[1440,1446,"PER"],[1510,1516,"ORG"],[1518,1525,"ORG"],[1526,1537,"PER"],[1564,1579,"LOC"],[1622,1631,"ORG"],[1680,1690,"ORG"],[1691,1705,"PER"],[1710,1723,"ORG"],[1724,1735,"PER"],[1766,1771,"MON"],[1773,1779,"ORG"],[1886,1900,"ORG"],[1901,1914,"PER"],[2013,2028,"PER"],[2063,2075,"PER"],[2114,2120,"ORG"],[2129,2142,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":27,"text":"Real Madrid have suffered a devastating blow on the eve of the new La Liga season, losing their goalkeeper Thibaut Courtois to an anterior cruciate ligament injury. The Belgian colossus has been pivotal to Madrid's success in recent years and Carlo Ancelotti hasn't had to think twice about who to start between the sticks. Courtois has been one of the world's leading shot-stoppers and his absence will be sorely felt by the Spanish side next season. Ancelotti needs a replacement for his number one, and has looked towards his old club Chelsea for a solution. Madrid have expressed their interest in taking Blues goalkeeper Kepa on loan for next season, a deal which Chelsea may be willing to sanction given their recent acquisition of Robert Sanchez. Here's why Real Madrid want Kepa at the Bernabeu. Considering Real Madrid will be relying on Andriy Lunin in their season opener against Athletic Club, Kepa's experience and quality would be a welcome addition to Los Blancos' squad. The Spanish stopper managed 39 appearances after reclaiming his starting spot from Edouard Mendy at Chelsea last year, including two encounters with Real Madrid in the Champions League quarter-finals. Kepa performed admirably given the criticism he has received in previous seasons, establishing himself as the club's guaranteed number one. Kepa ranked in the top 24% of Premier League goalkeepers for saves (3.16), save percentage (73.3%) and goals against (1.16) per 90 last campaign. He also boasted a +0.18 rate when it came to post-shot expected goals  minus goals conceded, suggesting that Kepa was performing significantly above average in terms of his shot-stopping. His ability and competence outside of his own penalty area could also be crucial for Madrid. He ranked in the top 17% of Premier League goalkeepers for number of defensive actions per 90 outside of his box (1.82), showcasing his quality in sweeping up opposition balls over the top. While not as significant in an Ancelotti team, it will still allow Madrid to press higher up the pitch, knowing Kepa can sniff out danger when direct balls are played in behind the defence.  Overall, Kepa provides Madrid with a cost-effective and experienced option. Add this to the fact that he is Spanish and knows La Liga intimately, and it seems like something of a no-brainer for Madrid, especially if they are only exploring a loan deal. Club Appearances Saves Save percentage Clean sheets Chelsea 162 379 69.4% 57 Athletic Club 54 134 67.7% 15 Real Valladolid 40 161 77.8% 12 Ponferradina 19 51 72.9% 8 *All stats courtesy of FBref feed Despite having initially prioritised a move for Sevilla goalkeeper Yassine Bounou, the asking price for the Moroccan appears to be a stumbling block stopping the deal from progressing. Attention has therefore turned to Kepa, who has also interested Bayern Munich, but Real Madrid don't want to rush into making a signing given the multitude of options potentially available to them. Kepa, however, is under serious consideration, with Courtois set for a long spell on the sidelines. At present, Madrid are said to only be interested in loaning the 28-year-old from Chelsea, although such a deal could have an option to buy or mandatory buy clause inserted into it. Given Chelsea's expensive pursuit of Moises Caicedo and Romeo Lavia, a permanent deal that could recoup some transfer funds may be preferential.","label":[[0,11,"ORG"],[67,74,"ORG"],[107,123,"PER"],[206,214,"ORG"],[243,258,"PER"],[324,332,"PER"],[452,461,"PER"],[538,545,"ORG"],[562,568,"ORG"],[609,614,"ORG"],[626,630,"PER"],[669,676,"ORG"],[738,752,"PER"],[765,776,"ORG"],[782,786,"PER"],[794,802,"LOC"],[816,827,"ORG"],[847,859,"PER"],[891,904,"ORG"],[906,912,"PER"],[967,979,"ORG"],[1070,1083,"PER"],[1087,1094,"ORG"],[1136,1147,"ORG"],[1155,1171,"ORG"],[1188,1192,"PER"],[1328,1332,"PER"],[1351,1354,"PCT"],[1358,1372,"ORG"],[1420,1425,"PCT"],[1583,1587,"PER"],[1747,1753,"ORG"],[1776,1779,"PCT"],[1783,1797,"ORG"],[1976,1985,"PER"],[2012,2018,"ORG"],[2057,2061,"PER"],[2145,2149,"PER"],[2159,2165,"ORG"],[2262,2269,"ORG"],[2330,2336,"ORG"],[2441,2448,"ORG"],[2457,2462,"PCT"],[2466,2479,"ORG"],[2487,2492,"PCT"],[2496,2511,"ORG"],[2519,2524,"PCT"],[2528,2540,"ORG"],[2547,2552,"PCT"],[2578,2583,"ORG"],[2637,2644,"ORG"],[2656,2670,"PER"],[2808,2812,"PER"],[2838,2851,"ORG"],[2857,2868,"ORG"],[2972,2976,"PER"],[3024,3032,"PER"],[3084,3090,"ORG"],[3154,3161,"ORG"],[3260,3269,"ORG"],[3291,3305,"PER"],[3310,3321,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":28,"text":"Kepa Arrizabalaga has confirmed he hopes to seal a permanent move to Real Madrid after joining the Spanish side on an initial loan from Chelsea. After Thibaut Courtois went down with a serious knee injury, Madrid began searching for a new goalkeeper and eventually settled on Kepa, who joined on Monday in a loan deal which does not include the option for Madrid to make the move permanent. Even though there is no purchase clause in Kepa's loan contract, the 28-year-old made it clear he is looking to stay in Madrid for the foreseeable future. \"I really hope Real Madrid will keep me at the end of the season,\" he told a press conference when asked if he wants to stay at Madrid. \"Today is the first day of my assignment. We have time, we'll see.  \"Hopefully with my performance I can make that happen.\" feed Madrid president Florentino Perez was eager to welcome Kepa, who he described as \"one of the best goalkeepers in the world.\" \"Dear Kepa, welcome to your new home. We know very well what it means to you at this moment and how hard you have worked to be able to defend the jersey and the crest of Real Madrid,\" Perez said. \"We're delighted to have you on board because you're one of the best goalkeepers in the world and we want to continue building on one of the most successful cycles in our history. \"You're also one of the great Spanish goalkeepers. This may be one of the most important moments of your whole professional career and, we hope, of your life. Your hard work, your talent, your commitment, the tireless support of your family and, of course, the will to be a member of the best club in the world have brought you this far. \"You will now experience the emotion of playing at the Santiago Bernabeu stadium, where you will understand its magic and where you will feel the passion from Real Madrid fans, surrounded by a unique fan base that gives their all for Real Madrid. Don't have any doubts, our fans will support you in taking on this challenge that is part of your biggest dreams. Dear Kepa, there are only a few who can experience the emotions that you are about to experience. This new period begins here with this crest full of trophies and unrenounceable values.\"","label":[[0,17,"PER"],[69,80,"ORG"],[136,143,"ORG"],[151,167,"PER"],[206,212,"ORG"],[276,280,"PER"],[356,362,"ORG"],[434,440,"PER"],[511,517,"ORG"],[561,572,"ORG"],[674,680,"ORG"],[811,817,"ORG"],[828,844,"PER"],[866,870,"PER"],[942,946,"PER"],[1106,1117,"ORG"],[1120,1125,"PER"],[1705,1722,"LOC"],[1809,1820,"ORG"],[1884,1895,"ORG"],[2016,2020,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":29,"text":"Liverpool are ready to match Chelsea   s offer for Southampton midfielder Romeo Lavia, 90min understands, with the transfer battle between the Premier League giants continuing. The two clubs have already been at war over Brighton & Hove Albion   s Moises Caicedo in recent days. Chelsea have been pursuing the Ecuador international for months, but it was Liverpool who first agreed a deal with Brighton for a British record fee of  £111m on Friday. Even then, it remained Caicedo   s preference to join Chelsea and the Blues, who had not previously offered more than  £80m, refused to throw in the towel. As it stands, Chelsea are now confident of finalising an agreement with Brighton in excess of the Liverpool offer already accepted. But Caicedo wasn   t the only player that Chelsea looked set to beat Jurgen Klopp   s team to. feed Liverpool, in need of midfielders after letting Jordan Henderson, Fabinho, Naby Keita, James Milner and Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain all leave this summer, had earlier seen three bids for Lavia rejected by Southampton     they had been holding out for  £50m, with Liverpool   s best offer totalling  £45m. Suddenly, Chelsea came on the scene and submitted a  £48m bid for Lavia before raising that offer to  £55m - a fee which left the Blues confident of getting a deal done. 90min now understands that Liverpool are ready to make a fourth Lavia offer that matches Chelsea   s bid for the 19-year-old Belgian, who has played only 36 senior club games in his career. As far as Southampton are concerned, they are happy with the developments and keen to see how this bidding war between Chelsea and Liverpool plays out. Lavia, meanwhile, is yet to make known his preference one way or the other, having held positive talks with both clubs.","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[29,36,"ORG"],[51,62,"ORG"],[74,85,"PER"],[87,92,"ORG"],[143,157,"ORG"],[221,243,"ORG"],[248,262,"PER"],[279,286,"ORG"],[310,317,"ORG"],[355,364,"ORG"],[394,402,"ORG"],[432,437,"MON"],[472,479,"PER"],[503,510,"ORG"],[515,524,"ORG"],[568,572,"MON"],[619,626,"ORG"],[677,685,"ORG"],[703,712,"ORG"],[741,748,"PER"],[779,786,"ORG"],[806,818,"PER"],[837,846,"ORG"],[885,901,"PER"],[903,910,"PER"],[912,922,"PER"],[924,936,"PER"],[941,964,"PER"],[1020,1025,"PER"],[1038,1049,"ORG"],[1085,1089,"MON"],[1096,1105,"ORG"],[1132,1136,"MON"],[1148,1155,"ORG"],[1191,1195,"MON"],[1204,1209,"PER"],[1240,1244,"MON"],[1264,1273,"ORG"],[1308,1313,"ORG"],[1335,1344,"ORG"],[1372,1377,"PER"],[1397,1404,"ORG"],[1508,1519,"ORG"],[1617,1624,"ORG"],[1629,1638,"ORG"],[1650,1655,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":30,"text":"Chelsea have agreed a British record deal of  £115m with Brighton & Hove Albion to sign midfielder Moises Caicedo, sources have confirmed to 90min. Just hours after their Premier League opener with Liverpool at Stamford Bridge, which ended 1-1, Chelsea reached an agreement with Brighton over their top summer transfer target. Caicedo is now due for his medical in London after which point he will put pen to paper on an eight-year contract which will also have an option for another season. The news of the agreement brings to an a frantic few days which has seen Chelsea beat Premier League rivals Liverpool to Caicedo's signature. Chelsea had been pursuing Caicedo all summer but up until last week refused to make a bid of over  £80m, with Brighton demanding at least  £100m for the South American midfielder, until Liverpool suddenly made an offer on Thursday evening and agreed terms on a deal worth  £111m. feed With Caicedo due for a medical on Merseyside on Friday, Liverpool looked to have beaten their top-flight rivals to his signature, but it then emerged that the 21-year-old had informed Brighton of his unwillingness to finalise a move to Anfield as he preferred to join Chelsea. Although Liverpool's offer remained on the table, Chelsea began talks and soon became confident of finally bringing Caicedo to Stamford Bridge. Now Chelsea have agreed a deal worth  £115m which will see them break the British transfer record once again. The Blues paid  £106m for Enzo Fernandez in January but are set to exceed that figure for Caicedo. Brighton will receive  £100m in guaranteed money from Chelsea with a further  £15m in add-ons, while the Seagulls will also retain a sell-on clause. Meanwhile, 90min understands that Chelsea believe they are well placed to finalise a deal to bring Southampton's Romeo Lavia to the club. Both Chelsea and again Liverpool have agreed fees with the Saints worth around  £55m for the Belgian international midfielder.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[46,51,"MON"],[57,79,"ORG"],[99,113,"PER"],[141,146,"ORG"],[171,185,"ORG"],[198,207,"ORG"],[211,226,"LOC"],[245,252,"ORG"],[279,287,"ORG"],[327,334,"PER"],[365,371,"LOC"],[565,572,"ORG"],[578,592,"ORG"],[600,609,"ORG"],[613,622,"PER"],[634,641,"ORG"],[660,667,"PER"],[733,737,"MON"],[744,752,"ORG"],[773,778,"MON"],[820,829,"ORG"],[907,912,"MON"],[924,931,"PER"],[953,963,"LOC"],[975,984,"ORG"],[1103,1111,"ORG"],[1155,1162,"LOC"],[1187,1194,"ORG"],[1205,1216,"ORG"],[1246,1253,"ORG"],[1312,1319,"PER"],[1323,1338,"LOC"],[1344,1351,"ORG"],[1378,1383,"MON"],[1450,1459,"ORG"],[1466,1471,"MON"],[1476,1490,"PER"],[1494,1501,"DAT"],[1540,1547,"PER"],[1549,1557,"ORG"],[1572,1577,"MON"],[1603,1610,"ORG"],[1627,1631,"MON"],[1650,1662,"ORG"],[1709,1714,"ORG"],[1732,1739,"ORG"],[1797,1810,"ORG"],[1811,1822,"PER"],[1841,1848,"ORG"],[1859,1868,"ORG"],[1891,1901,"ORG"],[1916,1920,"MON"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":31,"text":"90min  rounds up the latest  transfer news, rumours and gossip circulating around the world... Paris Saint-Germain have accepted an offer from Al Hilal for Neymar. (RMC) Alternatively, Neymar is excited about the possibility of rejoining Barcelona. (SPORT) Manchester United have approached Bayern Munich over signing Benjamin Pavard. (Sun) Real Sociedad have supposedly dropped their interest in out of favour Manchester United midfielder Donny van de Beek. (Mundo Deportivo) Ex-Manchester United captain Harry Maguire is yet to agree personal terms with West Ham on his proposed switch to east London. Odilon Kossonou is a  £30m alternative. (Sun) Moises Caicedo's proposed contract with Chelsea is set to run until the summer of 2031 with an option for a ninth year. (Fabrizio Romano) Manchester United have had a scout watching Nice pair Jean-Clair Todibo and Khephren Thuram, the latter already heavily linked with Liverpool. (Get French Football News) Ahead of his move from Brentford, David Raya was spotted walking through the media mixed zone at the Emirates Stadium after Arsenal beat Nottingham Forest in their season opener. (football.london) manual Brighton are tipped to go after Leeds midfielder Tyler Adams to replace Caicedo. (Independent) Other \"leading Premier League clubs\" have also now been alerted to Adams being available once more. (The Athletic) Barcelona are close to agreeing a deal with Manchester City for Joao Cancelo that would take the form of a loan with option to buy. (Relevo) Kasper Schmeichel could return to the Premier League to join Chelsea as a replacement for Kepa Arrizabalaga if he completes a loan move to Real Madrid. (Guardian) Tottenham have been tipped to break their transfer record to sign what is described as an \"A-list replacement\" for Harry Kane after he joined Bayern Munich. (Football Insider) West Ham star Lucas Paqueta has been dubbed the top transfer priority at Manchester City following the injury suffered by Kevin De Bruyne in the club's season opener. (talkSPORT) Manchester City are also hoping to sign Belgian winger Jeremy Doku as a replacement for Riyad Mahrez after he left for Saudi Arabia. (Mail) West Ham are expected to make an offer for Montpellier forward Elye Wahi, who is also linked with Chelsea and Eintracht Frankfurt. (L'Equipe) Former Chelsea and Manchester United midfielder Nemanja Matic is tipped to leave Roma after a breakdown in his relationship with Jose Mourinho. (Mirror)","label":[[0,5,"ORG"],[95,114,"ORG"],[143,151,"ORG"],[156,162,"PER"],[165,168,"ORG"],[185,191,"PER"],[238,247,"ORG"],[250,255,"ORG"],[257,274,"ORG"],[291,304,"ORG"],[318,333,"PER"],[336,339,"ORG"],[341,354,"ORG"],[411,428,"ORG"],[440,457,"PER"],[460,475,"ORG"],[480,497,"ORG"],[506,519,"PER"],[556,564,"ORG"],[591,602,"LOC"],[604,619,"PER"],[626,630,"MON"],[645,648,"ORG"],[650,666,"PER"],[690,697,"ORG"],[732,736,"DAT"],[771,786,"PER"],[788,805,"ORG"],[832,836,"ORG"],[842,859,"PER"],[864,879,"PER"],[920,929,"ORG"],[932,956,"ORG"],[981,990,"ORG"],[992,1002,"PER"],[1059,1075,"LOC"],[1082,1089,"ORG"],[1095,1112,"ORG"],[1138,1153,"ORG"],[1162,1170,"ORG"],[1194,1199,"ORG"],[1211,1222,"PER"],[1234,1241,"PER"],[1244,1255,"ORG"],[1272,1286,"ORG"],[1324,1329,"PER"],[1358,1370,"ORG"],[1372,1381,"ORG"],[1416,1431,"ORG"],[1436,1448,"PER"],[1505,1511,"ORG"],[1513,1530,"PER"],[1551,1565,"ORG"],[1574,1581,"ORG"],[1603,1620,"PER"],[1652,1663,"ORG"],[1666,1674,"ORG"],[1676,1685,"ORG"],[1791,1801,"PER"],[1818,1831,"ORG"],[1834,1850,"ORG"],[1852,1860,"ORG"],[1866,1879,"PER"],[1925,1940,"ORG"],[1974,1989,"PER"],[2020,2029,"ORG"],[2031,2046,"ORG"],[2086,2097,"PER"],[2119,2131,"PER"],[2150,2162,"LOC"],[2165,2169,"ORG"],[2171,2179,"ORG"],[2214,2225,"ORG"],[2234,2243,"PER"],[2269,2276,"ORG"],[2281,2300,"ORG"],[2303,2311,"ORG"],[2320,2327,"ORG"],[2332,2349,"ORG"],[2361,2374,"PER"],[2394,2398,"ORG"],[2442,2455,"PER"],[2458,2464,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":32,"text":"90min  rounds up the latest  transfer news, rumours and gossip circulating around the world... West Ham could pull out of negotiations to sign Harry Maguire from Manchester United as the deal is taking considerable time to complete. The two clubs agreed terms on a  £30m fee last week but progress in finalising the transfer has been slow. (Guardian) Despite agreeing to a  £60m deal with Southampton, Liverpool are set to miss out on the signing of Romeo Lavia to Chelsea. The Reds were also beaten by the Blues to Brighton's Moises Caicedo. (The Athletic) Chelsea recently pulled out of a deal to sign Tyler Adams from Leeds, while Liverpool had also been linked, but he is in line to join Bournemouth as the Cherries are set to activate his  £20m release clause. (BBC Sport) Saudi Pro League clubs are interested in signing Arsenal defender Gabriel Magalhaes. Should the Brazilian depart, the Gunners could turn to Manchester City's Aymeric Laporte or Crystal Palace's Marc Guehi. (Daily Mirror) Bayern Munich, Chelsea, Manchester City, Manchester United and Real Madrid rejected the chance to bring in Neymar from PSG, with the Brazilian now set to sign for Saudi side Al Hilal. (Independent) Tottenham are set to make an opening bid for Gent starlet Gift Orban, who is seen as a long-term replacement for Harry Kane. However, they want to sell players before prioritising incomings. (Evening Standard) Another striker on Tottenham's radar is Folarin Balogun, who will be allowed to leave rivals Arsenal for  £50m this summer. (Gazzetta dello Sport) manual Chelsea are close to finalising personal terms with Crystal Palace forward Michael Olise and are looking to sign the Frenchman for roughly  £45m. (Evening Standard) Barcelona boss Xavi is willing to sanction a move for Joao Felix, but only if they sign a right-back and attacking midfielder first. (AS) Newcastle are interested in signing a left-back and are eyeing loan moves for Arsenal's Kieran Tierney and Chelsea's Marc Cucurella. (Telegraph) Bayern Munich hold an interest in Manchester City backup goalkeeper Stefan Ortega, but it's not clear whether or not he'd want to leave the Premier League champions. (Sky Germany) The Bavarian giants are also keen on former Manchester United goalkeeper David de Gea, who is currently a free agent. (The Sun)","label":[[0,5,"ORG"],[95,103,"ORG"],[143,156,"PER"],[162,179,"ORG"],[266,270,"MON"],[341,349,"ORG"],[374,378,"MON"],[389,400,"ORG"],[402,411,"ORG"],[450,461,"PER"],[465,472,"ORG"],[474,482,"ORG"],[503,512,"ORG"],[516,526,"ORG"],[527,541,"PER"],[544,556,"ORG"],[558,565,"ORG"],[604,615,"PER"],[621,626,"ORG"],[634,643,"ORG"],[692,703,"ORG"],[707,719,"ORG"],[745,749,"MON"],[767,776,"ORG"],[778,794,"ORG"],[827,834,"ORG"],[844,861,"PER"],[892,903,"ORG"],[918,935,"ORG"],[936,951,"PER"],[955,971,"ORG"],[972,982,"PER"],[985,997,"ORG"],[999,1012,"ORG"],[1014,1021,"ORG"],[1023,1038,"ORG"],[1040,1057,"ORG"],[1062,1073,"ORG"],[1106,1112,"PER"],[1118,1121,"ORG"],[1173,1181,"ORG"],[1184,1195,"ORG"],[1197,1206,"ORG"],[1242,1246,"ORG"],[1255,1265,"PER"],[1310,1320,"PER"],[1389,1405,"ORG"],[1426,1437,"ORG"],[1447,1462,"PER"],[1500,1507,"ORG"],[1513,1517,"MON"],[1532,1552,"ORG"],[1561,1568,"ORG"],[1613,1627,"ORG"],[1636,1649,"PER"],[1701,1705,"MON"],[1708,1724,"ORG"],[1726,1735,"ORG"],[1741,1745,"PER"],[1780,1790,"PER"],[1860,1862,"ORG"],[1864,1873,"ORG"],[1942,1951,"ORG"],[1952,1966,"PER"],[1971,1980,"ORG"],[1981,1995,"PER"],[1998,2007,"ORG"],[2009,2022,"ORG"],[2043,2058,"ORG"],[2077,2090,"PER"],[2149,2163,"ORG"],[2176,2187,"ORG"],[2233,2250,"ORG"],[2262,2274,"PER"],[2308,2315,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":33,"text":"Liverpool are among the clubs interested in Leeds midfielder Tyler Adams, 90min understands. However, it is Bournemouth who have taken the biggest steps towards a deal so far. Jurgen Klopp   s side have signed both Alexis Mac Allister and Dominik Szoboslai to strengthen in midfield since the end of last season. But with Jordan Henderson, Fabinho, James Milner, Naby Keita and Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain all leaving, getting additional bodies in has still been important. Liverpool had been in hot pursuit of Romeo Lavia and then Moises Caicedo. Three bids were made for the former, who is now on course to join Chelsea from Southampton in a deal worth up to  £55m. The latter has already signed for Chelsea after the Londoners gazumped Liverpool   s accepted  £111m offer, which would have broken the British transfer record, with a  £115m bid of their own. The Reds still have plenty of potential options to recruit a midfielder and time left to do it before the transfer window closes. One they are keeping tabs on is Adams, who also nearly became a Chelsea player prior to the Lavia and Caicedo sagas reaching a conclusion. feed As 90min reported at the time, Chelsea triggered the  £20m release clause in Adams    contract with Leeds. The United States international then travelled to London for talks but ended up returning to west Yorkshire when negotiations collapsed at the same time as Lavia and Caicedo talks accelerated.","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[44,49,"ORG"],[61,72,"PER"],[74,79,"ORG"],[108,119,"ORG"],[176,188,"PER"],[215,234,"PER"],[239,256,"PER"],[322,338,"PER"],[340,347,"PER"],[349,361,"PER"],[363,373,"PER"],[378,401,"PER"],[470,479,"ORG"],[507,518,"PER"],[528,542,"PER"],[610,617,"ORG"],[623,634,"ORG"],[658,662,"MON"],[698,705,"ORG"],[712,725,"ORG"],[735,744,"ORG"],[759,764,"MON"],[833,838,"MON"],[857,865,"ORG"],[1019,1024,"PER"],[1051,1058,"ORG"],[1079,1084,"PER"],[1089,1096,"PER"],[1134,1139,"ORG"],[1162,1169,"ORG"],[1185,1189,"MON"],[1208,1213,"PER"],[1231,1236,"ORG"],[1238,1255,"ORG"],[1288,1294,"LOC"],[1331,1345,"LOC"],[1394,1399,"PER"],[1404,1411,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":34,"text":"Erik ten Hag has admitted that he wants Manchester United to make a few more signings during the summer transfer window. The Red Devils have been one of the busier Premier League teams thus far this summer, spending big to sign Andre Onana, Mason Mount and Rasmus Hojlund before their first Premier League game of the season against Wolverhampton Wanderers. There have also been plenty of outgoings too, with Anthony Elanga, David de Gea and Fred among the players let go, while Harry Maguire could be set to follow suit with the club recently accepting a  £30m bid from West Ham United for the defender. feed Speaking at his pre-match press conference ahead of Monday night's clash with Wolves, Ten Hag admitted that is keen to sign more players. \"I will always want more [players]! But I think every manager you could ask would also want more. But it is about the mentality; in top football we are talking about the demand, the absolute maximum. Because we demand that from our players and, in their defence, they expect it from us,\" he said. \"We are looking for the perfect situation but you never get the perfect situation. Then you have to come into your place and work for that, maybe with not the perfect situation but the perfect results.\" With Maguire set to leave,  Ten Hag may get his wish as 90min  recently reported that Man Utd are set to enter the transfer market in search of some centre-back cover. Jean Clair-Todibo, Perr Schuurs, Jarrad Branthwaite and Edmond Tapsoba have all been linked, while the club are also in talks with Bayern Munich over Benjamin Pavard too.","label":[[0,12,"PER"],[40,56,"ORG"],[121,135,"ORG"],[164,178,"ORG"],[228,239,"PER"],[241,252,"PER"],[257,271,"PER"],[291,305,"ORG"],[333,356,"ORG"],[409,423,"PER"],[425,437,"PER"],[442,446,"PER"],[479,492,"PER"],[557,561,"MON"],[571,586,"ORG"],[688,694,"ORG"],[696,703,"PER"],[1253,1260,"PER"],[1276,1283,"PER"],[1304,1309,"ORG"],[1334,1341,"ORG"],[1416,1433,"PER"],[1435,1447,"PER"],[1449,1467,"PER"],[1472,1486,"PER"],[1547,1560,"ORG"],[1566,1581,"PER"]],"Comments":[]}
{"id":35,"text":"Chelsea have announced the British record transfer of Moises Caicedo from Brighton, moving for  £115m and surpassing the  £106.8m spent on Enzo Fernandez in January. Caicedo has signed an eight-year contract at Stamford Bridge until 2031. \"I am so happy to join Chelsea!\" the 21-year-old said. \"I am so excited to be here at this big club and I didn   t have to think twice when Chelsea called me, I just knew I wanted to sign for the club. It   s a dream come true to be here and I can   t wait to get started with the team.\" It   s only ever been Chelsea. pic.twitter.com\/LCYf6A2BQr Co-sporting directors Laurence Stewart and Paul Winstanley said: \"Moises has proved himself as a standout player in European football over the past 18 months, and we are thrilled to add him toMauricio Pochettino   s squad. \"Moises possesses a rare midfield skill set and is a player we   ve been targeting for some time. We believe he will make a significant impact at Stamford Bridge this season     and in the years ahead.\" Caicedo only joined Brighton in 2021 for as little as  £4m and spent part of his first year with the club on loan at Beerschot in Belgium. But his rise to becoming one of the best midfielders in the Premier League has been rapid, going from little known prospect to the most expensive player in British football history in the space of just one year. Chelsea have been interested in Caicedo for many months, but until recently their best offer for the Ecuador international was a maximum of  £80m. Liverpool then looked to have won the race with a  £111m offer, before Chelsea came back to the table.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[54,68,"PER"],[74,82,"ORG"],[96,101,"MON"],[122,129,"MON"],[139,153,"PER"],[157,164,"DAT"],[166,173,"PER"],[211,226,"LOC"],[233,237,"DAT"],[262,269,"ORG"],[379,386,"ORG"],[549,556,"ORG"],[607,623,"PER"],[628,643,"PER"],[651,657,"PER"],[777,796,"PER"],[809,815,"PER"],[954,969,"LOC"],[1011,1018,"PER"],[1031,1039,"ORG"],[1043,1047,"DAT"],[1066,1069,"MON"],[1128,1137,"ORG"],[1141,1148,"LOC"],[1210,1224,"ORG"],[1362,1369,"ORG"],[1394,1401,"PER"],[1463,1470,"ORG"],[1503,1507,"MON"],[1509,1518,"ORG"],[1560,1565,"MON"],[1580,1587,"ORG"]],"Comments":[]}
